INDOXXI
Support dengan like & share :)
Men.
For as long as they live.
they will never stop questioning
why they are here
and their purpose of existence
in this world.
And when the time comes.
our choices
will be remembered by the people
until
the doomsday.
Choices to keep on living
beyond their crippling flesh.
their stifling bones.
and their frailing skin.
The noblest choice will be bestowed
upon those believers.
Their handsome rewards
await in heaven
soon enough.
A mining facility in Bongsun. Pahang.
was raided by the authorities
in the effort to cripple
drug manufacturing
by the narco-occult terrorist.
the group called Al-Minas.
The raid also led to a shootout
between the two parties.
severely injuring the group's leader.
Husyairi Ibrahim.
Currently. he is in ICU
at Pahang General Hospital.
I know this is illegal.
But garbage bags? Really?
Nice 'boat'.
Boat?
No wonder you use garbage bags.
You can't even tell a boat from a yacht.
This is Taqiyya!
We have to adapt!
Your uncle must be proud to see
how you apply his teachings.
My uncle?
So where is he now?
If you want to taste Husyairi's heaven.
watch your mouth!
Don't accuse.
Let's go!
You ungrateful punk!
Hey!
Do you think you'd get
anything without me?
You need me. I don't need you!
You piece of shit!
You are nothing without me!
What are you doing?
Get inside!
Hello. everyone.
Welcome to our big feast.
Our special for tonight
is methamphetamine.
But before we get started.
let me introduce and also thank
Commissioner Adli Apdal.
Director of Jakarta
State Intelligence Agency.
Sir.
We have a big catch tonight.
All thanks to Mr. Adli's intel.
Or more specifically. Mr. Adli's mole.
-Riky.
-Jijoe!
Where is it?
Unit leader. this is Parameter Team.
Our Indonesian friends are watching.
Don't mess around. Let's do it right.
Parameter Team. please be on standby.
GET OUT NOW!
Okay. let's go.
Hey. where are you going?
Our business is done. Jijoe.
Betrayer!
We're dead.
Quick!
I'm going to kill you!
Damn it!
Get back out there.
I need you to distract the cops.
I'll triple your payment if you survive.
Now!
Tango. on your right!
Dan. follow me.
Let's go! Hurry!
Police!
-Secure the area and get them out of here.
-Yes. sir.
Hey!
Khai!
Get out!
-Okay! I'm getting out! Don't hurt me!
-Hurry up!
Get back!
Okay.
Let the lady go.
-You don't have to do this.
-Drop your gun!
We can work this out.
-We promise--
-Now!
Okay!
All of you!
I think I knock her down.
Don't do that. Khai.
Put it down. Khai.
-Dan. put your gun down.
-Sir.
With all due respect.
-what if she shoots us?
-Put it down. Mat Dan.
Stay down!
Some mole. huh?
They knew we were coming.
No sign of Riky at all.
How many drugs did we score?
-Forty kilograms.
-Forty kilograms?
That's a lot!
They say it's the fourth time
Riky has gotten away.
There's something we don't know.
Mat Dan! Come here!
He's calling.
Yes. sir?
Were you taking selfies?
Do you think that's for a show?
It's drugs.
Here. let me teach you something.
Give me your gun.
What's this?
A gun. sir.
-What's a gun?
-Pardon?
-A weapon.
-A weapon is?
-A tool to catch the criminals. sir.
A tool to catch criminals.
Look what we've done to that poor lady.
-We?
-The criminals use this too.
But when we use it. we as cops
must protect citizens. not endanger them.
But what if they shoot us
and we don't have our guns?
And what if she gets shot?
Do you want to be responsible?
I understand. sir.
Keep it.
Go and apologize to her.
Yes. sir.
That was intense.
You were so dramatic.
You should teach at the police academy.
Luckily he said "tool."
or else I would slap him.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
GET OUT NOW!
Do you know
why Riky is always ahead of us?
Because he has a mole!
That corrupt dog!
Calm down. Rian. We still need you inside.
Whoever this mole is.
I'm sure he has told Riky about me.
Yet Riky is pretending not
to know about my identity.
Should I talk to them individually?
You leave that rat to me.
But you have yet to complete your mission.
No. sir.
I was almost killed by cops tonight.
Going back to Riky?
It's like getting out of the frying pan
and into the fire.
This mission went from six to nine months.
It has been more than a year!
Give me a bit more time.
I'm running out of time. sir.
Does anyone else know about this?
Okay.
I'll call the headquarters
and get you out immediately.
All right?
Don't worry.
Yes?
Sir?
You're a good cop. Rian.
But cops need to know how to adapt.
Do you know how I always get my catch?
If you want to lure your target.
find a way to do it.
You must be willing
to sacrifice everything.
Tonight. we got 40 kilograms from Riky.
You were supposed to be the front!
But lately. you are meddling
way too much now.
Wait. sir.
I can adapt.
I can learn how to adapt. sir.
So you're finally willing to learn.
CHERONG ISLAND
Saif.
Riky involved the cops again.
Did it affect our business?
No. but I think he's strayed
from our cause.
It's not the time yet. Najr.
We'll deal with him later.
Tonight. we keep vigil.
Tomorrow. we'll fight.
Inform our brothers.
Dad. I will make you proud today.
Goodness. you're fast!
Thirteen to one.
What is this. a badminton score?
Give me a break!
Badminton is nothing compared to this.
Come on. Let's make it 15 sets.
Hold on! I need to catch my breath.
Do you think
the crooks out there take breaks?
-They don't do time-outs. Come on!
-Hey.
Those punks!
Get them to carry these
tires and gas tanks.
No more excuses.
This will be the death of me!
If I die here.
who's going to buy you dinner tonight?
Why would you buy me dinner?
Hey. I know why you wear that ring.
Don't play dumb.
Bring your mom along.
Tonight's dinner is on me.
We'll have seafood.
Hello.
Sir.
Have a look.
Do you recognize him?
Five o'clock this morning.
Look who showed up.
This woman?
So she's Adli's mole?
This was at 5.45 a.m.
She came out alone.
The cleaner found Adli's body.
Two shots to the chest. One to the head.
Forensics found this too.
Don't know whose cell phone it is.
Looks like a phone log.
-One number keeps showing up.
-Can you trace the number?
Of course.
We even got its last coordinates.
Come.
There.
Cherong Island?
You guys go take a peek.
Remember. just a peek.
-Gather information and report back.
-Yes. sir.
I heard you had trouble
with cops last night.
You shouldn't listen to gossips.
This is MStar radar
from the Americans in Afghanistan.
Smell it. Fresh off the line. right?
Positive.
Riky Kumolo. Damn. he's got nerves.
He just got raided last night.
and he's back at it again.
What about the others?
I've never seen them before.
Sir. over there.
Sani.
Our special guest is here too.
So. we're good?
Not yet.
What the hell?
My goodness!
-Lah. did you get that?
-Yes.
-All of it?
-Yes. sir.
It's time.
Be careful.
Lah. go to the village. Get a line.
-Call Captain Wazir. Tell him everything.
-Yes. sir.
Dan. you stay here and watch them.
Khai. you and I. We'll tail Riky.
Saif. I have Riky.
We are heading back now.
Good. Najr.
Get everyone ready. now.
Drop it.
Drop it!
We're on the same side.
-You're arrested for drug trafficking.
-This is a mistake.
Also for murdering an Indonesian cop.
I'm a cop from Indonesia.
Do you think you can fool us?
Think you can fool us?
Let's talk at the police station.
I'm after Riky too. If he gets away--
Don't worry.
No one's getting away this time.
Hello. Captain Wazir?
Hello sir?
Damn it!
Listen. about last night's operation.
you only got close to Riky because of me.
You put a gun to a civilian's head.
That's enough to arrest you.
I had no choice.
I'm an undercover
and you wouldn't believe me.
How I wish Adli were still alive.
He could help me clear the air.
Regretting yet?
Today. you'll be one step
closer to paradise.
You know what to do.
Let's move!
Hello. sir. I'm sorry. sir.
The line was bad just now.
Okay. so...
Suddenly. they kidnapped him. sir.
Sir?
Saif. please.
I only involved the cops
as I had guaranteed.
Do you know the traits of a hypocrite?
Saif. my faith is unyielding.
I would not...
Are you telling the truth?
If that's true.
then I have a greater plan for you.
Sir. there's something wrong.
The guys we saw are coming here.
I told Captain Wazir about Riky.
But the phone line was bad.
-Where's Khai?
-Not here yet.
Hello there. Looking busy. I see.
Where's the party at?
Hey. what are you guys up to?
What are you...
What's that?
-What's with the smoke?
-Why are you asking me?
Spit it! What's with that smoke?
I swear I don't know!
Sir!
Lah. watch her. Dan. follow me!
What do we do? Sir!
Find wet cloths and cover your face!
Let go of me!
Hey!
Sit!
Sit there!
Sir. there's a clothesline outside.
Dan. keep your gun away.
Don't bring it out yet.
We don't know how many they are out there.
Where?
Lah!
Lah! Stop shooting!
Get in here! Lah! Here!
Get in here. quick!
Lah!
Sir. we're surrounded!
It's your order. sir!
Where's your gun?
-Your gun and holster!
-But. sir...
Now!
Hands up! Get up!
Hands on your head!
Lah?
Hey!
Wake up!
My friends!
Where are my friends?
Where are my...
Listen carefully.
In the name of Messiah. we. the Al-Minas.
have seized Kampung Pasir Beras
on Cherong Island.
We have no less than 200 hostages.
If we see any police ships or boats.
or any vehicle within
a 10-kilometer radius of this island.
you will see what happens.
Sir.
Everyone on standby?
Yes. sir. UKAP and UNGGERIN are ready.
QRF?
PGM Kuantan is gathering assets
from Terengganu and Kelantan.
and so is the 7th Battalion.
They'll be ready in 2 hours.
Have we verified the hostage count?
Census records show 447 residents.
including those who are staying in
and working outside the island.
There are about 200 hostages.
-Have you checked with the satellite team?
-Yes. sir.
It was at 1640 hours.
The satellite detected clouds
surrounding the village.
But on a closer look.
it's actually gas instead of clouds.
The smoke was to lure people
out of their homes.
We haven't identified the gas as of yet.
But if it's CS.
it's possible they have got everyone.
So he's not lying about the numbers.
It's true. according to the SAT.
All right. everyone.
This is our head of operations.
SAC Dato' Azizat Mansur.
Introduce yourself
and mention your designation.
Let's put the protocols aside.
I want to know who the perpetrator is.
We got their leader.
They were quiet for three months.
Now. they're back at it.
We're compiling Al-Minas profiles. ma'am.
Have you run
the face and voice recognition?
-Not yet. sir.
-Why not?
-We were waiting for you.
-"Waiting for me"?
Waiting for me to do it?
Listen.
We have 200 lives in our hands.
Our enemy is ahead of us.
I want you to sit tight.
open your eyes and ears.
Give me everything you got.
-Yes. sir.
What are you waiting for? Now!
Sir. I've checked the hall.
Khai is not here.
Dan. don't call me "Sir."
I don't want them to know
that we're cops. Understand?
-Have you checked the back?
-Yes. sir.
Sorry. Sani. Khai is not in here.
Do you want to stitch it yourself?
How long was I out for?
Three hours or so.
It's hard to find a place to fix you up.
Where are my friends?
I don't know.
All I saw was chaos out there.
Are you ever going to stop lying?
Do you think I'm a part of this?
I came here for Riky. not with Riky.
I'm undercover in his organization.
I know it's hard for you to believe.
If only I could force Riky to talk.
I can prove everything.
But thanks to you and your friend.
even that's a dead end now.
Rian.
Khai.
You saved my life. so we're even now.
You're leaving just like that?
What choice do I have?
Hey.
It's a mess out there.
I don't know if you're telling the truth.
but if you're really a cop.
I need you to act like one now.
Get out! I'll teach you a lesson!
-Move!
-No. sir.
You liar!
Get out!
Hey. answer me.
How many were there in the house?
Why did you lie?
Do you think I'm a fool?
Please. sir!
This is the second round-up of villagers.
We'll follow them.
They will lead us to Riky and my friends.
Then what?
We'll gather intel
and inform the headquarters.
Then we wait for help.
Saif. we've gotten everyone from the east.
We're sending them to you now.
Check again.
Make sure the place has been emptied.
Roger.
It's strange. right?
You woke up today.
The sun rose like any morning.
Yet here you are in the midst of doomsday.
I'm curious.
I have always wondered.
Why wouldn't God reveal
when the doomsday is?
But now as I gaze upon his servants.
I've finally understood.
It's your faith!
You wear your faith like a mask!
But don't worry.
Tonight. all your sins will be forgiven.
But if anyone gets in our way...
This will be the last thing you hear.
Excuse me. sir.
Sir.
Well...
In case you aren't aware.
there are old folks and kids here.
They are sick. starving and thirsty.
If you're not giving us food.
you can give us some water.
Enough?
Enough!
So do you all want water?
Give it to them.
-Stop it!
-We're drenched!
Hafsyam Johari. or Saif.
Husyairi's the mouthpiece of Al-Minas.
This is the hand. The sword.
He was last spotted at the Bongsun raid.
But we couldn't find the body.
This is him five years ago.
He was a professor at UTM.
Double PhD in chemical engineering
and Islamic studies.
You'd think with such accolades.
he'd be a man of true faith.
He is a man of faith.
That's why he had the gut
to mastermind six attacks before this.
There were 200 casualties.
That excludes casualties
by the drugs he manufactures.
Guys. return to your posts.
Okay. let me cut to the chase.
The government won't compromise
with terrorists.
Once they make their demands.
I can stall them but not for long.
Commander Maarof.
How's our infiltration plan?
It's ready. ma'am.
According to the MET report.
it'll be overcast in four hours.
We should only go in
when it's completely dark.
The first team Northside.
the second-team Eastside.
Ma'am!
We've got a call from the island.
This is SAC Azizat Mansur.
To whom am I speaking?
This is Azizat Mansur.
the head of the Anti-Terrorism Unit.
-To whom am I speaking?
-Terrorists?
That's a harsh allegation.
You know that it's frowned upon
when women become leaders?
Am I speaking to Hafsyam Johari?
What do you think?
How can we help you. Hafsyam?
Such arrogance.
You sound just like the Pharaoh.
I just want to know how we can help.
Perhaps we can negotiate peacefully.
Now you want to know what I want?
Your ignorant mind won't understand.
Wait until the sun finally rises
from the West.
Wait until the Great Fire
burns from Yemen.
Wait until Angel Gabriel heralds
the arrival of Messiah.
Then only on that day
will you know what I want.
I understand what you're saying.
How about this?
I can set up a dialogue for you
to voice out your--
Hey. woman! You listen to me.
We're not doing business.
I'm not negotiating anything.
You will have to return
Imam Husyairi to us.
For every hour
that Imam Husyairi's not here.
I will kill two hostages.
Hafsyam.
You know Husyairi is still critical.
It's risky discharging him from the ICU.
You have no power
over life and death. Azizat.
One hour from now!
You know this will take time.
Plus. it involves diplomatic relations
between two countries--
So you need more time?
-Very well.
-Hafsyam?
Hafsyam! Hello? Did we lose him?
No. ma'am.
Hafsyam?
Hafsyam! Saif!
You. waterboy. get up.
You forked tongue liar. get up!
I won't repeat myself. Get up!
Sir!
Sir! Please. sir!
Sir. please!
-Sir. please. Take me instead. please!
-I'll do anything you want.
I'll do it now!
You don't have to do this. Saif!
Dad!
-Please!
-Have mercy on us!
-Please.
-Pity us!
You said you need more time?
Now you have two hours.
Sit!
Five guards at the main door.
Three by the hostage hall.
There's another problem.
That.
-No way.
-A radar with a five-kilometer radius.
It detects all movement.
There's no way out.
We need to inform the headquarters.
How?
All phone lines are down.
There's a way.
We can't negotiate with this psychopath.
Maarof.
Our infiltration plan.
Can't we go in earlier?
Yes. ma'am. But I must warn you this.
We expect a 20 to 25 percent
casualty rate.
I suggest we send a recon team first.
For what. Maarof?
Do you think he won't kill anyone
in these two hours?
Yes. but we don't know their capacity.
We cannot just ambush. ma'am.
Ma'am.
If he realizes that we won't give in.
won't it get worse if we don't act fast?
If we ambush now.
people may die.
But if we wait.
we don't know what will happen.
Okay.
He refused to negotiate. right?
Fine.
Send our unit in now.
Zairi. come in.
You scum. You brought the cops here!
Najr!
Enough Najr! Enough!
Hey. I said stop! That's enough!
Don't you see. Saif? My brother was shot!
-But no one heard a thing!
-Enough!
We will find your brother's killer.
but not by acting like a deranged bitch!
Don't forget our purpose here!
What is going on there?
I think only one man
can drive someone so crazy.
Try again.
Still nothing.
What on earth?
Everything is plugged in.
Try to check the "sekring."
I mean the fuse. over here.
Fuse.
Almost five clicks. ma'am.
Saif. there's an incoming boat.
Check it.
We're connected.
Abrar. take your men there.
Khalif. you take the other side.
Najr. you take the far side.
-Saif. come in.
-Come in.
Something's wrong. The Telco tower is lit.
Check the battery. it might overload.
Plug out all cables except the phone wire.
It's the yellow one.
It's 999. what's your emergency?
Go take a look. Najr.
Get them before the cops arrive.
Everyone else. stick to the plan.
Sani. something's up.
I have a plan.
Ma'am. we've got an emergency call.
It's a police officer from IPD Kuantan.
He says he's on the island.
How did he reach us?
Through emergency hotline.
His ID details are valid.
This is SAC Azizat Mansur.
Ma'am. I'm Inspector Khairul Salleh.
Narcotics. Kuantan IPD.
They have a trap here.
What do you mean?
They have radars.
If you send anyone in.
they will know.
Contact our unit now.
Janggut Hitam to Janggut Putih.
We're at East Sector.
Roger. We're en route to North Sector.
Ma'am. radio silence.
We cannot reach them.
Satellite phone? Have you tried that?
What do I do now. ma'am?
What you need to do
is drop that phone now!
-Inspector!
-We're disconnected.
We tried using the satellite phone
but to no avail.
Are you alone?
-I'm alone.
-Don't lie!
Turn around slowly!
Drop your weapon!
I said I'm alone!
What the hell are you waiting for?
Drop it!
Our guests are here.
Stay down!
Blue house!
Cover me!
Janggut Putih!
We need backup! Taking heavy fire!
Okay. chief! We'll be right there!
Contact at 12!
Zali!
Man!
Where?
Damn it!
Blue house!
I'll take him!
Damn it!
Don't do anything stupid. Dan!
Stay here! Don't move!
I can fight! This is my choice. not yours!
You! Quiet!
Me? He's noisy not me!
What the hell?
You're going to get us all killed!
Hey. do you hear me? I said shut up!
-Sit down!
-Sit here like a coward? Like you?
Hey. sit down! Do you want to die?
This is the first time
I'm agreeing with a criminal.
Dan. please. Sit down.
And wait for what? For you to speak up?
What do you want to say?
I say...
Now!
Saif!
Put your hands up!
Listen to me.
Tell them to drop their guns.
Your fight is over!
Drop your weapons!
If I don't. what would you do?
-Don't test me.
-I dare you. Shoot me.
I said drop it!
We're cops.
We've spoken to Dato' Azizat
from the headquarters.
We're here to help. Okay?
Where are the rest?
Where are they?
They're surrounded.
Follow me.
Do you think these men are my slaves?
They're slaves to my agenda.
They're crusaders.
They've vowed to die as martyrs
than to live another second in this world.
-Wait here and keep a lookout.
-Okay.
Damn it. Khai!
I have an idea.
Come on!
-You want me to take it?
-I'll do it.
Chief! The backdoor's clear!
Okay. Everyone out!
Don't shoot!
We're cops.
Drop your guns!
If you surrender.
you'll betray me and our cause.
Sir. what do we do?
-So you're cops?
-Shut up!
Let's shake things up a bit.
Shall we. sir?
My dear warriors.
aim your weapons at the hostages.
Hey!
You can drop your weapons.
or go ahead and shoot me instead.
These hostages' lives are in your hand.
What say you?
Decide. then. I'll count to ten.
One.
-Two.
-What are you doing?
Three.
Four.
-Five.
-Sir?
Six.
Seven.
I only counted to seven.
The Royal Malaysian Police.
you guys are impressive.
Dan! Dan!
Dan!
Behold!
Behold the sacrifices your cops make
for the people and country!
We're no different. you and I.
We both have principles.
You have your convictions as a cop.
And me.
-my greater purpose.
-You and I are not the same!
Your place is in hell!
And you're sure yours is in heaven?
If I really belong in hell.
why in the God's will
am I the one standing.
while you're on your knees?
Don't worry.
You put a gun to my head.
You gave me a chance to prove my faith.
Now I'll return the favor.
Pull the trigger.
and I will let everyone go.
including this little dog beside you.
I'm sorry.
You took an oath to protect lives
and save people.
I admit I was wrong. I'm sorry.
You did nothing wrong.
Not even one mistake.
It's your job. keep at it.
Finish the job!
Don't do this. Let us all go.
Please.
Pull the trigger.
Pull the trigger!
I'm sorry. I was wrong.
We're nothing alike.
Your principles aren't comparable to mine.
Chuck him with the rest of the bodies.
We might need him later.
Yes. ma'am.
Five operatives were killed.
One is critical.
Any other way to get us out?
Put pressure on it.
Understood. ma'am.
There's no extraction.
We're ordered to sit tight and wait.
Arshad!
Arshad! Mikael!
Wake up. Arshad!
Arshad!
Damn it!
There's an incoming call from the island.
Do you know the traits of a hypocrite?
A hypocrite breaks a promise.
You know what I want.
and I have given you enough time.
Saif. I can explain. We just wanted to--
Listen up.
You have betrayed all these people!
Now. pay attention!
Our agreement has changed.
I'll give you two more hours.
After that. I will kill everyone!
Saif.
Let me... Saif?
-Saif.
-We're disconnected. ma'am.
Tell Abrar to set up the bombs.
Unless we teach them a lesson.
they will keep messing with us.
Saif!
Saif. they got away.
They took our weapons and radio.
Why are you here?
-My work here is not done.
-Precisely!
Your work here is absolutely not done.
Do you not see the will of Messiah?
You should have been dead.
Yet here you are. breathing.
I won't stop until they're all dead!
Revenge has made you weak. Najr.
Now's the time to be strong.
Rise from the ashes!
Prove to Messiah
why you deserve this second chance.
Fix him up.
Rafael.
Change all walkie frequencies.
I was at a briefing
for a regional operation.
There was a Malaysian.
His ring was like yours.
This is not mine. I just take care of it.
Why do you believe me?
Your friend was so eager to lock me up.
I didn't say I believe you.
I guess I want to believe you.
Meaning?
I got this ring a day
before the owner went undercover.
He asked me to keep it.
Three years in a drug syndicate.
and he never came back.
Before we knew it. he was hooked.
When the headquarters pulled him out.
he was in bad shape.
Addicted.
I believe that like him.
you must have your reasons too.
Your old partner?
You could say so.
How is he now?
He was shot.
Sorry.
Bad things keep happening on this date.
Nothing I do is ever right.
I suppose this day is cursed.
The day is not over.
There's still time.
Are you guys hungry?
No. thank you.
Take it.
Thank you.
Hello there.
Greetings to the two cops
wandering around out there.
-Are you infidels?
-Syam.
Hello there.
Hello.
That's more like it.
I've killed one of your friends.
I have one more with me now.
The one with the big nose.
Listen to me. you prick.
-If you lift a finger--
-Listen to me first.
What are you fussing around out there?
You know you can't stop me.
Am I right?
Am I talking to the wall?
-I'm listening.
-You listen but don't answer.
What the hell do you want?
The hell do I want?
I like bold people like you.
Unlike your friend here
who tries too hard to be a cop.
You have two options.
Surrender. and your friend will be spared.
Or?
I will toss your friend's body
all around this island
so that you can pick it up piece by piece.
I'll think about it.
We have to do something.
Our orders are to stand down.
Let me speak to Dato' Azizat.
Inspector Khairul. please calm down.
Didn't you hear what he just said?
He's going to kill my partner at any time!
My partner is a cop.
Just like me. just like you guys.
Are we just going to let him die?
I should've left you to die just now.
Ma'am. I want to discuss our next steps.
My partner is held hostage
with a lot more others.
I don't know what your plans are.
But as long as they have that radar.
there's only one end to this story.
Inspector.
we don't negotiate with terrorists.
We have principles.
-You understand?
-For saving lives?
Do we use the same principle for that?
My point is there are six of us.
Why not send us in?
Send you in for what? To die?
That's not what I am insinuating.
-We give what they want.
-We don't compromise--
Yes. ma'am. We let them think
that they're getting what they want.
Once they're distracted.
we can move in quietly.
Then you send an assault team.
We'll defend the hostages from the inside.
Inspector Khairul.
I must admit that you're brave.
But there's just six of you.
Including your partner. seven.
While they have--
A lot more will die
if we don't do anything.
But I cannot order you all
to take such a big risk.
If you really want to go in.
you have to voluntarily do it.
Dan?
Dan!
Thank goodness. Dan.
You...
Dan?
I'm dead. sir.
My goodness.
I'm dead.
Why?
Do you fear death. sir?
Didn't you take an oath
to save them?
What happened to your promise?
This isn't only for my friend.
There are 200 people to think about.
If the headquarters try to attack again.
not only will Al-Minas banish.
the hostages will too.
I'm not trying to be a hero.
I just cannot live with myself
if I don't do something.
This is crazy.
I cannot decide for everyone.
You make your own choice.
Zul?
If we do this.
it's like we're digging our own graves.
There are so few of us left.
But if you're going in.
I'll have your back. sir.
Mikael?
How many more have to die?
You know what I mean. right?
Tonight alone. Sab. Paan. Riko. Kamal.
Syahrul. Arshad.
But then again.
I don't want their deaths to be in vain.
Zali?
What are we waiting for?
In all my years of service.
I've never made a decision like this.
But I remember the day I took the oath.
I swore to save lives.
Okay. I'm in.
What about your friend?
My mission was simple.
get Riky and go home.
But now that's on hold.
Promise me. you'll keep your word.
Understood.
Fate has brought us together tonight.
Let's see what fate has in store
for our enemy.
Zali. suit them up.
Comms. vest. weapons.
-Whatever we have.
-Yes. sir.
Attention. unit leader.
The package will arrive in one hour.
As soon as the package arrives.
the assault team will follow
five clicks behind.
Make sure all the hostages
are secured before they arrive.
Otherwise. many will perish.
I repeat.
As soon as Husyairi arrives.
I want a safe passage out.
If you lie to me.
you will pay.
Yes. Saif.
It's all clear.
Now you listen to me.
Until Husyairi arrives.
if you kill anyone.
I don't care if you have hostages.
I will be the one to make sure
that you pay.
Saif.
Saif. what is this? Saif!
Didn't you say
that your faith is unwavering?
Your uncle will arrive soon.
Please. Saif.
Saif.
I am more useful if I'm alive!
Please. Saif!
You really are useful. Riky.
Do you remember the story of Abraham?
Only the sacrifice of a kin
can please our God.
You must be proud. Riky.
Your uncle will rise again
because of you.
Take all of his blood.
Don't waste a single drop.
One tango. south block roof.
Another on the east roof.
Take them out.
Okay. move!
Damn it!
Zali. over here.
It's a C-4.
Can you handle it?
No problem. sir.
Rafael. is that the only boat?
Yes. Saif. Just that one.
Sani. are you okay?
He told me to pull the trigger. Khai.
What are you talking about?
It's all my fault. Khai.
I couldn't do it.
I couldn't...
Sani.
Sani. focus.
There are four special forces guys
out there.
The hostages are all secured.
We only have to keep guard
until the assault team arrives.
Sani. I need you right now.
He gave me a choice. Khai.
I could have shot myself
and saved these people.
-But I didn't do anything!
-Goodness. Sani.
He was right. I'm not fit to be a cop.
-I'm not fit to be a cop.
-Don't listen to him.
-Why do you listen to him?
-Khai...
Sani!
Sani. I'm here because...
I'm here because you're my partner.
Khai...
Look. Khai. Mat Dan is dead.
He died and I didn't do anything.
I just watched him die.
He's playing with your head. Sani.
Do you think if you pulled the trigger.
he would release them?
That's what you think!
That's what he wants you to think!
Get up!
-Khai!
-Get up!
-Leave me alone! Go!
You don't get it. Khai!
These people died in front of me.
And I didn't do anything.
I just watched them die! I just watched!
I'm completely useless!
Many more will die
if we don't do anything now.
Please get up. Sani. Please.
Khai!
You don't get it!
What did I say?
You don't understand.
You were not here.
You don't know how it feels.
My younger brother died
right in front of me!
That's not all.
I was the one who shot him!
I'm reminded of what I did every day!
This is our job. What can we do?
We take on the worst when others can't.
It's a cruel world and you know it.
We endure it.
We soak it all up.
Who will clean it up if not us?
Sani. if I didn't do that.
my mom would have died.
Even I would have been dead too!
You're well aware of all this!
Do you still remember this tool?
When you're ready.
find me.
Sir.
This tool has no conscience.
Criminals use it too.
But for us cops.
what is this tool for?
Your partner?
We can just proceed.
Let's clear the rest.
There's another problem.
The west side looks busy.
There are two tangos outside.
I'm sure there's more inside.
There's one on the roof.
North-west block.
Can't we take them down from here?
No. Too risky.
We don't know how many there are inside.
What if we go around the building?
That could work.
We can clear the inside first.
It's too far.
They can spot us anytime.
There's another way.
Help. sir! The rope is loose!
-Stop! Don't move!
-The rope. sir.
It came off. Please tie it back!
Please tie it back! Tie it for me!
I'll shoot you!
Are you crazy? Saif wants him alive!
-North-west block clear.
-Let's go!
Looks like he's gone crazy.
I want food. Do you have any food?
Please tie this back.
I don't want to get scolded
when they see my hands like this.
Saif really drove him insane.
Hey!
Is someone messing with your brain?
With my brain? Yes. there is.
Oh. really? Who?
-Your mom.
-You punk!
Mikael.
Zul. Zali. We head north-west. now.
Give me a hand.
Don't die on me.
Get up!
Tell them you were working with Adli.
Tell them.
Get up! Tell them everything!
-Rian.
-Get up!
Get up!
Rian.
-Get up!
-Enough!
That's enough.
Enough.
Rian. I'm sorry.
You were right about Adli.
Here's the proof.
Keep it safe.
This proves your innocence.
GET OUT NOW!
Rengau Main.
The package arrives in five minutes.
Take your positions.
We have secured the hostages.
I repeat. The hostages are secured.
The assault team is on the move.
ETA. 30 minutes.
Good luck. Rengau Main.
Thirty minutes.
That's a long time. You sure we can hold?
They're coming.
We have to hurry!
Help untie the rest.
Get everyone into the room.
Help the others.
Keep your head down.
All of you will testify this today!
This is a testament
that God is pleased with our fight!
Saif. something's wrong.
There is a bomb!
Now!
Najr!
Ma'am. Hafsyam's on the line.
Leave it. Don't pick up.
Listen. my fellow brothers.
They are screwing with us!
We will not let these infidel punks
insult our religion!
Split up and move out!
And we will send these dogs back to hell!
We will fight until we breathe our last!
Saif!
-Left side!
Khai. it's full. There's no more space.
For now. stay down.
Keep your heads low. Stay low.
Listen up. You. you and you. follow me.
Stay low. Stay calm.
I'll be right here to protect you.
Here! Take these. Make a barricade.
Hurry!
Where's Saif?
Saif. what do we do?
Najr. now is the time for you to rise.
Prove to Messiah that you're strong.
They're breaching from the west.
Last one. Get them in and stay low!
-Syam. do you copy?
-West side.
Hey.
Zali. are you okay?
Sir. Zali's down!
I repeat. Zali is down!
Damn it!
Charge!
-Khai!
-Don't let them get close!
West block! I need support!
I'm going inside! You stay here!
Cover me!
Now!
Khai!
Get up. Khai!
Help!
Quick!
What do we do now?
Get inside. Everyone. inside!
Squeeze in! Just do it!
-Go in.
-You?
Just go!
Everyone. stay down!
Don't you see that this is all fated?
If God is really on your side
and not on mine.
why are you on your knees again
while I'm still standing?
Here we are again.
Here?
Here.
Not six feet under.
Maybe our work here is not done.
I keep seeing
Mat Dan's mom's face.
Lah's wife's face.
It's hard.
There are things we can let go.
And there are things we must hold on to.
I'm sure they'd want us
to focus on the job
and look after those who are still alive.
Hey.
Speaking of which.
how's that Indonesian cop doing?
Is she doing okay?
The last time I saw her
was when we gave our statements.
She seemed okay.
That's a relief.
Hey.
We wouldn't be here if it wasn't for her.
Remember that.
I feel like a goat.
We eat nothing but leaves.
Hey.
For your birthday that day.
I promised you seafood.
It's not that I don't want to
or can't afford it.
but seafood is bad for healing wounds.
I shouldn't complain.
Well. I can roll with it.
As long as the cursed day is over.
I'm curious about
what will happen next year.
-Next year? Again?
-Why?
Are you sick of me?
No. but how long do we have
to deal with this?
For as long as we can play the part.
For as long as we're in demand.
For as long as they need us.