101 FM Radio, we play the best music
in Jakarta.
You're still on 101 nonstop music,
with me Ricky Rahim.
Streets in Jakarta are ridiculous
right now, so be patient.
Try not to use your horn
and make it more stressful.
To help you relax, I give you a song
from FSTVLST titled "Ayun Buai Zaman",
only on 101 FM Jak Radio.
Son of a bitch!
What is it, Alam?
This guy’s pissing me off.
Your party is responsible.
Stealing foreign money.
Omitting knowledge transfer
from contracts.
You and the old regime
are huge exploiters.
#LogicRules.
Politicians who steal to get ahead
have brains the size of a mini peanut.
That’s hate speech.
Be careful. We have laws for that.
Hiding behind Internet laws.
You spineless douchebag!
Grill the idiot, Alam!
-I’m behind you, bro!
-Let’s get moving.
Can you please focus on driving?
Yeah, honey. Sorry.
Your wife’s in labor,
put your phone down!
Okay, honey.
You want me to give birth in this car?
Guys like Faisal are everywhere, you know?
Always accusing foreigners of stealing.
When, in fact,
we’re the corrupt ones.
We don’t use our brains.
It’s important for me to comment.
Alam, there are more important things.
What about our budget?
You sure we’ll go with this hospital?
We could go with the clinic.
It makes more sense financially.
Watch out, idiot!
Hey, you’re the idiot! Dimwit!
Alam, cut it out!
He called me an idiot!
And he kicked our car.
Just drive, will you?
Don’t mind the motorbikes.
Hon, I may be an idealistic blogger
running an indie publishing house,
but I’m a hot daddy-to-be
who knows his priorities.
Jokes? Really?
Take a chill pill.
Alam, please!
-Whoa!
Please, just drive.
Drive, or I will give birth
in this goddamn car!
I promise.
Okay.
Everything will be just fine, okay?
Doctor Rivat, to the ER please.
Doctor Rivat, to the ER.
-Hon…
-Yeah?
Can you adjust the cushion?
I need to lay back.
Like this? Careful. All good and comfy?
Yeah.
Don’t diss other people
about responsibility,
when you’re stealing people’s jobs
with your pseudo-publishing.
Non-margin, bro?
I thought you were progressive. Thief!
Shit.
Why is your T-shirt inside out?
You were having a contraction,
I didn’t care what I’d look like.
Besides, the Chinese say it's good luck.
Amen to that.
Zee Zag must be bummed.
Their ideas are spread hypocritically.
While my publishing house, Kalam Vortex,
is trying to acquire the legal rights.
In the name of freedom of information,
non-margin publishers are here.
Don’t compare us with the tiny logics
of information corporations.
Hon, come on.
You’re also playing with your phone.
I’m not playing, I’m working!
Not engaging in some Twitter war!
My work pays for this. Come on.
Number 314, proceed to counter.
A thief is a thief.
-No need to use fancy lingo
-Alam,
-that's our number.
-like corrupt politicians.
Alam, focus!
Okay.
For God’s sake.
No use talking about responsibility
with a guy who knocked up his girlfriend
so he could marry her.
#NotGettingIt
Guess @amrinpasaribu will never get it.
We have to fight
for the in-laws’ blessings!
Hi, there.
-Yes.
-VIP Normal Birth Package, please.
-All right.
This is the brochure. And this is my ID.
-Fill this out, please.
-Yes.
Smile, please?
Smile.
Okay, thank you.
I can take my wife to have our baby
in a proper hospital.
Not like you. With a midwife.
#KeepCalm #BeResponsible
Sari, what are you doing here?
Hunting for Pokémon.
I’m here for you, silly!
-So nice of you.
-Are you here alone?
No, Alam’s over there.
He’s booking our room.
Oh, so this @alamerdeka guy
is a pot calling the kettle black.
-Sir.
-Hold on.
Empty vessels make the most noise.
Sir?
Blame the one banging on
the vessels, dude!
Sir, I’ve counted twice.
It’s not enough money.
What do you mean not enough?
-Not enough.
-It’s 500 bucks, right?
The hospital’s anniversary discount?
Here let me count it for you.
The promotion period has ended.
Since when?
The discount is for the whole month.
Since today.
It’s the first day of the next month.
But today is the 30th, lady.
Here, I’ll count…
Sir, it’s for February.
Yes, it’s a leap year,
but the month still ends on the 29th.
The VIP price
is now back to $1,500.
Maybe you’d like to discuss
with your wife…
She doesn’t know about this!
I’m dead.
Hon, come here.
Look, Sari has brought us everything.
Blankets,
pads.
You don’t have to go back to the store.
Say thank you.
I’m going for my Friday prayer.
But that’s so not you.
People can change, right?
I’m about to be a dad.
Thanks.
I get it. He’s turning into a new man.
Let’s hope it lasts.
Don’t be a jerk!
Where am I going to get the money?
This is nuts.
Who parked here? Who parked here?
Oh, I see.
Government official’s car
can park anywhere.
My wife’s pregnant,
and we got a shitty parking spot.
@alamerdeka I demand that you
apologize publicly,
and take all your false accusations back.
What a douchebag!
I have to get back to the office.
Right now?
Yup. They’ve been texting me,
I might come back later today.
-Bye.
-Thanks, Sari.
Keep me updated.
I will.
You wait here, okay?
Hold on.
-You’re good?
-Don’t be too long.
-I won’t.
-Your bag?
Don’t hide, @alamerdeka.
Or my lawsuit will find you.
I’m not hiding, you asshole!
Allah, have mercy.
I meant, a hole.
Someone’s hiding in a hole.
Contractions?
I had one earlier, but not now.
Didn’t you have sex
with your husband this morning?
Huh?
No.
It’s the best natural induction, you know?
And it feels good, too.
You don’t believe me?
-Hello, Alam.
-Mr. Fuad?
-Yes, Sir.
-How's the Zee Zag book?
-What took you so long?
-Be patient.
-I can't.
-We don’t have to rush.
-Have you heard of slow living?
-How about I’ll slowly kill you?
-Don’t be like that.
-What?
Look, I’m in the middle
of my Friday prayer.
I’m trying to get in the front row.
-More reward from God, they say.
-Alright.
-Bye now.
-Bye.
Cover up, boy!
You’re in a mosque, not the beach.
-Thank you.
-Yes.
I’m sad. People are talking about
our personal life.
Come on, Alam. Let that book go to Amrin.
Peace be upon you.
All praise belongs to Allah.
Peaceful mind, peaceful heart.
#SpiritualFriday
With my firstborn,
it took me 20 hours.
20 hours?
20 hours of labor!
Imagine that.
But I’m wiser now.
This morning we did our hanky panky.
Our VIP room is ready.
It's him!
It’s so hard to get.
This hospital is like…
-Like what?
-A hotel in Bali during high season.
-Oh, like when we were there?
-Yes.
Our honeymoon?
You remember?
You want another honeymoon?
I do! I loved our suite.
MOM
Yes, Mom. No, not that one.
The one in Semanggi.
Yes.
You’re with Dad, right?
Usep and Tantri, too?
Don’t bring a crowd, please. Mom?
It’s all yours.
Peace be upon you.
-May Allah the Almighty…
-Isn’t he running for governor?
…give us guidance,
so we can vote for the ideal leader.
Look at the current situation.
Flooding everywhere,
poor people are being evicted
from their own homes.
I know where he’s going with this.
Everyone is angry.
Demonstrations every day. Why?
Because they’re disappointed!
I will fix it all!
So, with all conviction,
I am running for governor…
Interruption!
This is a place of prayer.
Not for political campaigns.
-What the hell is this?
-Can he be any more vulgar?
You might as well
try selling underwear on that podium.
-This is a place of prayer!
-Because it is a place of prayer,
-it deserves more respect.
-Come on!
Hey, let go of me, dude!
There’s a more dignified way to protest,
you know.
Just walk out, like me. Don’t be childish.
Why are you giving me a sermon?
Why do you care?
Of course, I care.
People like you give Islam a bad name.
Be critical logically. Not emotionally.
Don’t use your brain the wrong way,
like you wear your shirt.
Where are you?
I’m already on dilation two.
ACCOUNT BALANCE: $ 1.3
I’ll be waiting, okay?
Don’t meet me at the hospital.
If my wife finds out, I’m dead.
My family is on their way, too.
I’ll let you know.
Somewhere near the hospital.
-See you.
-Just a little bit more.
Okay, you’re good.
Good day, Madam, can I help you?
The 20th floor? That way.
One floor up. Thank you.
-Excuse me.
-Yeah?
Do you know any cheap places to eat?
Cheaper than the cafeteria?
There’s a place over there.
-Near the construction site.
-Yes.
A canteen. The food there is cheap.
-Like a food stall?
-That’s right. Over there.
-Thank you.
-You’re welcome.
-Hello.
-Alam, where are you?
-I just finished Friday prayer.
-It's stuck.
I spent a little extra time at the mosque,
praying for our baby.
Where are you now? What's that noise?
-Alam?
-Why did you turn it off, man?
The music was good.
I’m moving the car now,
so you don’t have to walk far
when you get out of the hospital.
That's not important, Alam.
Be patient, I’ll be right there.
But that's not important!
I'm already in the ER.
-Yes. I have to go.
-Hurry up!
Sorry about that.
Can I have a coffee? Sorry.
Alam, you’re lucky I was just about
to go out when you called.
I appreciate it.
So how much do I get for this?
As we said on the phone. Here.
I could give you more
for your car and laptop. But you said no.
How on earth am I going to pay for that?
I haven’t paid you
my last debt for my wedding.
Debts and logic don’t mix, dude.
Borrow what you need.
Sure, you’re getting interest out of it.
I’m killing myself paying for it.
What can I say?
I wouldn’t be doing this
if it weren’t an emergency.
600 bucks enough for your kid?
Should be enough.
I have to go.
Where are you going? Let’s hang out first.
My wife’s looking for me.
Can you get this coffee?
Man, he’s paying, okay?
If you need more, call me!
Sir, Ma’am, here’s your room.
Yes, thank you, Nurse.
Excuse me.
Hold on.
Alam, aren’t we getting the VIP room?
We’ll be here temporarily.
The VIP rooms are all occupied.
But my 500 bucks
are for the VIP room, right?
Yes, that’s right. But the rooms are full,
so we’ll be here for a while, honey.
Doesn’t matter to me, really.
Easy, Ma’am.
Easy.
Trust me, okay.
We’re not having money problems, are we?
No problems!
Alright?
Let me take care of some paperwork. Okay?
I’ll be right back.
Let’s change your clothes, shall we?
Lady?
Hey, lady.
I want to ask you about the discount.
Your brochure is misleading.
You should’ve put the exact date,
so it’s clear.
I’m sure I’m not the only one
who's fallen for it.
I should get the VIP room,
but now I’m downgraded to second class.
What do you have to say?
I’m sorry, Sir. It is clearly stated.
You should’ve read more carefully.
What do you mean? I did.
I read the form.
But look at this. Such tiny letters.
Now tell me, can you read this?
Yes, I can.
Well, you got healthy eyes.
What about those with eye problems?
If you really want to trick people,
use 3D glasses...
Sir, it hasn’t been an hour,
and you already asked
for an installment policy.
And I granted your request.
That sounds nice. I would’ve requested
an installment plan if I'd known.
It’s their responsibility.
The promo was unclear.
Second class is the same, I’m telling you.
Besides, the VIP rooms are all full.
Can I get the installment plan too?
I’m sorry, not possible.
Be careful, lady.
And God, you’re pregnant!
You’re putting yourself in danger.
-Your baby is your responsibility.
-Yes, Sir.
I know, I’m sorry.
-Just be careful.
-Thank you, Sir.
Yeah.
Can I have a glass? Just the glass.
The water’s free, right?
Hello, how about that book bidding?
I thought you'd called
to tell me you’re a father now.
Forget about the bidding.
What do you mean? I don’t get it.
-Mr. Ingkus has been transferred.
-But the tender is clear.
That is corruption.
The bosses are afraid of KPK.
The tender is still unclear.
Then what about Nandi?
We borrowed money from him for this bid.
Nandi is different from Ivan.
He’d literally rip off my balls. Shit!
I don’t know, man. I’m way over my head.
Don't be...
Crazy jerk!
How am I supposed to pay for the hospital?
Sorry. Personal problems.
What kind of hospital is this?
Where are the doctors and nurses?
-Usep! Tantri! Come here.
-Yes, Mom.
Are you sure we’re in the right hospital?
We are, Madam.
Where are the…?
Oh, hello, Emi. How are you?
-Hey, you’re here, too.
-How are you?
-Of course, why wouldn’t I be?
-You look so fresh. Look at those cheeks.
-You are so beautiful.
-So do you. You’re gorgeous.
-Dear, come here.
Dear. This is the boy’s mother.
-How are you? Are you well?
-He's good.
Such a handsome man.
-You’re so fresh. What’s your secret?
-Thank you.
-Is it the skincare from that website?
-Oh no, no.
I can’t get enough of online shopping
myself. Look at all of this.
-That’s so beautiful. The colors and all.
-I bought it online.
This old thing? I sewed this myself.
When I was pregnant with Alam.
-Oh my, that is old. Usep!
-Yes.
-Go find out where Mia’s room is.
-Where is Mia's room?
Bring clothes for Alam.
Dear, come here.
-I have to pee.
-Just wait, dear.
So what room is she in?
I can't stand it.
So all of your family is here?
No, they’re just relatives… Dear!
They happen to live nearby.
So they can come here directly.
And yours?
Such a tiny family. Just these two?
These are Alam’s neighbors and friends.
They’re here to help out.
-Oh, neighbors.
-Sir.
-Usep! So where’s the room?
-Bring clothes for Alam.
Huh?
Really?
Why not VIP?
Hello, little one.
-Hi.
-Honey.
All under control?
Yeah. All good.
Have you heard from the doctor?
Doctor Titi will be here
for the ultrasound.
Alam,
whatever happens, I want to have…
A normal birth.
Yes, I guarantee you that will happen.
-Yes.
Just like your mother. Six kids.
One as big as you.
All alone. All normal births.
I have to be that strong.
I have to do whatever it takes
for this baby. We have to fight for it.
Hey, don’t be vulgar.
What’s wrong with you?
You want the baby to have extra ears?
-Who are you coming with?
-With them.
Where’s your husband?
There he is.
Usep, Tantri, not so loud.
There’s another patient.
What’s going on?
Dad!
There you are!
-You’re stepping on my toes!
-Why are you standing there?
Relax. Sorry, there’s another patient.
-What?
-Sorry, another patient.
Stop saying sorry. Why aren’t you in VIP?
This room’s so tiny.
You need a proper room. This won’t do!
-You don’t have money?
-It’s not that.
-It's not that.
-You can always ask me and your dad.
-Mom!
-Mom,
Mom, it’s not that.
All the VIP rooms are full.
So we’re here temporarily.
What’s the problem?
-This is our first grandchild.
-God, this boy!
Of course I want the best for her.
And Doctor Titi is handling Mia.
The best doctor.
Promises, promises!
-Excuse me.
-Oh hi, doctor.
Mrs. Mia?
Doctor Titi is a man?
No, no, no.
Where’s Doctor Titi?
Doctor Titi is not available.
I’m the obstetrician on duty.
So young. Is he even capable?
Are you an intern?
A recent graduate?
I’m here for the ultrasound.
Could some of you wait outside, please?
I hope you don’t mind
waiting outside.
Yes, Nurse, yes.
-Sir? Excuse me.
-Oh, please, Doctor.
-Let’s draw the blinds.
-Yeah.
Uhm...
-Is it okay if I stay?
-Yes, Sir.
How is it, Doctor?
Yes, I’m checking.
Nurse, why do you keep staring
at my husband?
You’re Alam Merdeka, right? Right?
I’m one of your followers.
Follow me back, please!
What follower?
Twitter. He’s got tens of thousands.
48,000.
Did you go to all your check-ups?
When was the last time?
Uhm, when was it…
-You don’t know? When?
-Quite a while ago.
It’s a breech birth.
-Oh dear God!
The baby is big, too.
Mia, you should’ve gone to
your check-ups!
That’s it. We’re moving to VIP.
And having a C-section!
-Dad!
I’ve never meddled in your business,
because I trusted and respected you.
But can you not embarrass me?
Hey, Alam! Answer me!
Thank you, Doctor.
Everything okay?
Okay, Doctor.
-Thank you, Nurse.
-Yes, Ma’am.
-Wake up, Uncle.
-Give him some room.
Hold him.
-Easy, Uncle. Say a little prayer. Oh God.
-Give him some water.
-My cane! My cane!
-The cane.
Nurse, where is Doctor Titi?
She’s at a medical entrepreneurship
symposium
in London.
Don’t be so surprised, Sir.
It’s been four months
since your last check-up.
So it’s not our fault
if your schedule is messed up.
Absurd! Why is a symposium more important
than my wife giving birth?
How could she?
How is it just your business?
Your baby is getting as big as I am!
Look at your belly.
You just found out now?
I still want a normal birth!
Oh dear God, a normal birth.
Four kilos. You know how big that is?
It’s the size of a gallon of water!
Twice my thigh. As big as her thigh!
And a breech birth!
How is it going to come out? How?
Tantri, pack up.
-Hey, Tantri.
-Yes?
Don’t touch my things. Back off!
-You work for me, right? I said pack up!
-No!
-Mom, enough. Tantri, back off!
-Good riddance, Mia!
So next time, with your second child,
regular check-ups, okay?
Fine, you want war?
I’m not afraid. Remember, Nurse,
this is the era of social media
I have 48,000 Twitter followers.
I could tell the whole world this hospital
is crappy to its patients.
They’re mistreated. I’m tweeting it.
Very well.
If you want to deal with our lawyers.
Shit!
Just my two cents.
We have to use our social media wisely.
-Hey, Nurse! Come here.
-Yes.
-Is Doctor Titi really away?
-Yes, Sir.
-Is there another doctor?
-There is.
I want to speak to your head nurse,
or somebody.
Wait a moment, Sir.
Your dad?
Your dad never gave birth.
He never gave birth!
Dad, please talk to Mom.
Tantri, pack up her stuff.
What’s wrong with you?
-How?
-Sorry, Madam. All VIPs are full.
But relax, we’re on the baiting list.
-Yes, that’s what I meant.
-We’re next in line, right?
-Ten more patients.
-For God’s sake, ten?
When will we get in? Next year?
-Mom, chill!
-Is the AC off? So warm in here.
Mom, please calm down.
-Bring an AC from home!
-Dad.
Can I help you, Sir?
Well...
If Doctor Titi’s not available,
no problem.
But please get someone with her caliber.
Not a snooty ob-gyn boy.
This is my firstborn!
Sir, all our doctors
have the same qualifications.
You’re just saying that!
I need action! No one’s helping me out.
It’s because I’m not a VIP patient, right?
This is discrimination!
If you don’t calm down,
I’m calling security.
This is a hospital, not a hotel.
All patients get the same treatment.
So, please, you’re not being rational.
I want the best for my wife.
Will you help me out?
I’m tired here. Those are my in-laws.
What am I supposed to tell them?
And she’s so loud,
you can hear her from a mile away…
Okay, do you want me
to speak to your in-laws?
Don’t do that. You might as well kill me.
Just euthanize me now!
Mia, please have a C-section.
Don't mind about the money.
Your dad and I can help you.
Mom, give it up. I told you, no C-section.
The doctor said there’s nothing wrong
with me.
Is that so?
Lucky you’re not diabetic.
I’m about to have a heart attack here.
Right, Emi?
Don’t hurt your parents’ feelings.
Don’t be stubborn like your dad.
Hey, dear! Say something, dear!
Leave Dad alone.
You said it yourself, he never gave birth.
You have to listen to Alam, too.
The boy can’t even
wear his shirt properly.
Alam!
Yes, the boy. That’s what I said.
Alam! His name’s Alam,
and he’s my husband.
Yes, your husband, the boy.
Alam!
Yes, the boy’s your husband.
Your dad’s my husband.
Dad is Mom's husband.
Oh, hey, Mr. Alam.
-Doctor…
-Don’t worry about it.
We’re in the same boat today.
People see us as incapable.
I’ve been an ob-gyn for seven years.
But, I still have no kids of my own.
I’m still grateful, though.
Trying to live as a good person.
My wife once said to me,
“Every child comes from God.
So He will always pick the right person
to help with the process.”
Well, I guess that’s my destiny.
Just take it easy, Mr. Alam.
I’ll see you in delivery.
Yes, doctor.
No one’s here?
Another empty room? So strange.
Ah, here’s a bigger room.
-Hey. You’re the guy from before.
-Hi again, lady from before. Sorry,
I thought this room was empty.
-Can I help you, Mr. Alam?
-You startled me!
-Looking for a tweet material?
-No. Does she have this room to herself?
Yes, she does.
This part of the building is still empty.
You’re lucky, you know.
Mrs. Dian over there,
her husband is working in Dubai.
He left her.
She’s going through this alone.
Her family lives out of town.
-Wait a minute.
-Yes?
So the whole floor is empty?
Yes, the soft opening
was just three days ago.
Most patients prefer the other wing.
So, only a few rooms are occupied.
-Where’s marketing?
-5th floor.
-Now you startled me!
-Sorry. Thank you, Nurse!
No problem!
Everybody, we’re moving to a new room.
-Now?
-Yes, to a bigger room.
-VIP!
-Usep, Tantri.
Hm, this is the room? It’s bigger, yes.
-But, well, it’s still not VIP, is it?
-Mom.
Smells like paint in here.
Is this fresh paint?
Mom, chill, go sit down.
The smell can’t be good for you, Mia.
Dear, close your nose.
-Mom, it's fine.
-The room is huge.
Good job, hon.
Let’s take a selfie.
-How lame.
-Calm, Sir.
Here’s the caption. See?
How did we get this room?
This.
-So, here’s the deal, Sir.
-Yes?
According to my notes,
social media influencers
with around 50,000 followers
get $30 per tweet.
Okay. I may only have 48,000 followers,
but they are very active.
They’re all organic, no robots.
So every time I tweet,
they will respond and retweet.
Alright.
I’ll give you a special package.
How about 20 tweets? Deal?
-I don’t know.
-The 33rd floor is still empty.
A little promotion won’t hurt, right?
I guess so. Let me speak to my manager.
Can you wait here?
-Yes, I’ll wait here for the good news.
-Okay.
So, no more nagging
when I’m playing with my phone!
Now that’s smart. That’s my Alam!
This is so you.
-Alam.
-What?
Come here. Go make up with Dad.
-I will.
-Now.
-Later.
-Now. There’s no better time.
-One thing at a time, okay?
-Come on, Alam.
First things first. You go in labor, then…
Listen.
My relatives say Dad never laughs anymore.
But that’s because of the stroke.
Well, who gave him the stroke?
Because he found out I was knocked up.
Come on. Please.
-I will. Later, okay?
-I would be even more grateful to you.
-Please.
-Yes.
Gosh, it hurts. Rub my tummy.
-What is it?
-Nurse?
-Hey, you!
-Yes, Sir?
-Take care of my daughter!
-We'll be there ASAP.
Rub my tummy, damn it!
What took you so long?
Yes, let me take a look.
Please, help, Nurse.
Excuse me, Ma’am. Let me check.
What’s she doing to me?
It’s the next dilation. Dilation four.
-Praise God!
Thank you, Nurse.
I said rub my tummy. You have one job!
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, shit!
Hey, where are you going?
Hey, stupid head! Come here!
Where are you going?
Hey, stupid head! Hey!
Hey!
Why are you hiding from me?
Alam, listen to me.
It drives me crazy
when people talk about responsibility.
You and your job.
What kind of a job is it?
You wear shorts, you make calls.
What will people think of that?
What is your job anyway?
Stop giggling.
How am I supposed to believe in you?
Stupid head!
I’ve always known
you never believed in me.
When Mia got pregnant,
I never had the chance to apologize.
You couldn’t even speak properly!
And whose fault is that, stupid?
I was about to tell you
that I will be responsible.
I won't run away.
What is this?
What is that?
Wait, Dad!
What is this thing?
Let’s take another whiff.
So good!
I can even play golf now, see?
What is this?
Oh my God.
I came here so that you’d learn something
about responsibility.
Yes.
That’s a baby coming out of her!
Not some… poop!
Poop?
-Stop giggling!
-That’s your child!
Hey your mouth got twisted again.
Ouch, it hurts. Get up. Get up!
I’m not running from my responsibility.
I’m not going anywhere.
N2O is not a toy!
You understand?
People call it laughing gas.
It’s an alternative anesthetic
for surgery.
For normal births.
Not something to play with!
For laughing?
Hey!
It’s not a comedy show!
I apologize.
Not accepted! What is this, Idul Fitri?
You’re laughing,
but I'm the one management will be mad at!
If they find out,
they’ll kill me right now!
Poor guy.
Yes, poor me! Listen, you’re all grown up.
You’re an old man.
And what’s with your inside
out shirt and homeless pants?
I am so sorry, Sir.
Forget it.
Don’t let me see you back here again.
I’m warning you. I will not call security,
-I’ll have the army come and bomb you!
-Sorry, Sir.
“Sorry, Sir.”
Why did you run away
to Mia’s uncle in Surabaya?
How did you know that?
I know everything.
Listen, let’s call a truce, okay.
For my grandchild.
As long as you know what you have to do.
No more war between us.
All you have to do is trust me.
Everything will be okay.
Alright.
-But can I ask you one more thing?
-What?
Let’s take a selfie.
As a symbol of peace.
Let everybody see. Smile! Look happy!
Say cheese!
We’re leaving now.
Yes, take care.
Come on.
-We're leaving.
-Take care of her.
-Get your phone on stand by.
-I'm leaving now.
-Take care, dear.
-Thank you.
-Bye. Everyone.
-Bye.
Thank you, everyone.
Sari? I can do the revision,
no need to delegate to Coki.
Yes. Seriously.
But, can you help with my points?
Okay, bye.
I’m sad, you know.
You’re about to give birth
and you’re still working.
Typing away. It’s almost time.
How will you focus on the delivery?
I am focused.
-And that boy husband of yours.
-Alam!
I’m talking about his job, not his name.
Has he found a proper office job?
-Mom!
-What?
You’re so insensitive!
I thought she’d left with everybody.
Of course she hasn’t!
How was I supposed to know?
Everybody was saying goodbye.
I'm focused on you!
How’s Mia? Are you a father yet?
Erik, what are you doing here?
Well, aren’t you friendly?
I told you I was behind you.
Look.
Something's wrong with your shirt.
My shirt, my business.
You’re here for that politician,
aren’t you?
I saw his car in the parking lot earlier.
I’m here for you, bro.
Well, after that,
I’ll see Mr. Bimo from Commission I.
Heart problems. Bypass surgery.
Politics is hard, bro.
Listen, I’m actually here to help you out.
I know you’re fighting over a project
with Amrin.
You do it, I’ll give you a pre-order.
I have to go. Let’s go.
No, no.
I can manage. Go back to your friend.
Alam,
call this man.
He’ll win the governor election.
I’m on his team. Call him,
and he’ll order your book. Seriously.
What’s he going to do?
Just call him. Mention my name.
He can help you with that lawsuit.
What's the position you're after, man?
Tell me.
How could you think that about me?
My intention is pure.
I’m making up
for that time I beat you to the
Editor-in-Chief position.
-Say hi to Mia for me.
-Wait, what?
I have to go.
Aren’t you here to see Mia?
Yeah, maybe later.
Honey, can I borrow your laptop for a sec?
Where’s yours?
It’s in service.
I’m adding some extra RAM for speed.
But you had it with you earlier.
Yes, I did.
But I gave it to Gugun for service.
Gugun was here? When?
Earlier, he didn’t stay long.
I need to work on this important book
so I’ll get the advance soon.
Give it to him, child.
It's his opportunity.
I’ll guard it with my life.
Thank you, Dad.
Good luck.
Silly boy.
Nice room, right?
You can lie down and relax.
It still smells like paint.
Take care.
It's okay, dear.
-Mom! It hurts!
-What happened?
-What’s wrong?
-Mia!
Hold her hand.
What do I press?
-Which one?
-Press that one.
Nurse!
Let me check, Ma’am.
Alright.
Hold. Breathe.
Breathe.
-Don’t just stand around.
-Yes, Sir.
Dilation five!
Praise God!
I got carried away.
Hang in there, Ma’am. It’s almost over.
-Hello?
-Hello, is this Alam?
This is he.
I’m Nugraha, Faisal’s lawyer.
We would like to file a lawsuit,
because you have not shown
any good intention so far.
What’s your problem?
Looking good. Be careful.
Up, up. Be careful now.
Yes, be careful.
Can I have a glass, please?
Alright, up.
Up.
If you do not respond
to Faisal’s request within 24 hours,
we will serve you with the lawsuit.
Okay, lift it up.
Lift it up.
Watch out for the iron bar.
Hey! Watch out!
Never mind.
-Some more?
-I’m good, thanks.
Fine, leave it there.
She’ll have more later.
Mia, how can I change your mind?
Have a C-section.
No, Mom.
Why? The goal is the same.
To get the baby out.
I said, no, Mom.
If you and the boy have no money,
your dad and I will help.
We have money for you, don’t worry--
Mom, I’m having a normal birth.
End of discussion.
I knew it.
How did you know I was here?
Please. I gave birth to you.
I carried you for nine months.
I can find you anywhere.
What are you working on?
Just some work.
-Alam.
-Yes?
Can I have a light?
-For God’s sake.
-Why?
You can’t smoke in a hospital!
Behave, please.
Oh come on.
Here, have this.
-What’s this?
-Try it.
Hell.
I’m supposed to chew on this?
What am I, an old lady?
What’re you working on? Why so serious?
Zee Zag’s book.
Do you still remember this scarf?
Yeah. It’s as old as I am.
Grandma gave you the fabric...
Then what?
Don’t you get tired of telling that story?
Give me something else.
A fairy tale or something.
Because there’s a part
I haven’t told you yet.
What?
It was a tough time.
The doctor was about
to give me something to abort you.
He said it was a high-risk pregnancy.
But I was sure,
every baby deserves a chance.
We can never escape our children.
Never.
A child is more than just a blessing.
It’s not something you search for.
It’s something you receive.
You brought this child into the world.
Hey.
Don’t forget to eat.
Before you’re responsible for your child,
be responsible to yourself.
Okay? I’m going back in.
Ma, can I borrow five bucks?
Dear God...
-Here, take it all.
-Oh, some extra?
-Thank you, Ma.
-I’ll see you inside.
Okay.
What, Erik?
You’re still in touch with
the Forum Progress guys, right?
I need to mobilize a crowd.
You know the Kaliandri scandal?
I have to organize
a counter demonstration.
And I need a crowd.
They’re still radical, right?
Can you pull some strings?
This is the perfect angle. Human rights.
How many times have you asked me
this favor?
Same answer from me. No.
You need the pre-order
from my government friend, right?
You want to get paid or not?
I checked with the hospital cashier.
You’re still 400 bucks short, right?
Indeed.
Hey, Sir?
Where are you taking that trolley?
-Oh, no. Just my laptop.
-You can’t take it with you.
-Yes, sorry, Nurse.
-It's okay.
-Are you serious or not?
-I’m serious, Mr. Fuad.
-I'm not sure.
-I emailed you the pre-order.
You just prepare the schedule.
I’ll send over the text tonight
or tomorrow morning.
Good, send it.
See? I bet you’re smiling over there.
I can feel it.
It won’t be long now.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
FINALLY. A GOOD CAFETERIA MEAL
AFTER A WHOLE DAY WAITING FOR CONTRACTION.
AFTER A WHOLE DAY WAITING FOR CONTRACTION
Hey! Alam Tanjung.
Stay right there!
David has fled.
Boss Nandi is black and blue.
-Don’t you run away, punk!
-No, no.
Don't run, you son of a bitch!
How?
Dilation six.
-Really?
-Praise God!
-We’re getting closer.
-Thank God!
Mrs. Mia?
-Sister?
-She’s losing energy.
Hey, don’t run!
Hurry, get him
Hurry up!
Son of a bitch!
Let’s take a break. Chill.
Easy. Take a break.
Hey, don’t run!
Hey, don't run!
Run!
Hey!
-Where are you going to go?
-Come on, Mom!
Mom, come on! Which floor?
Let me press the button.
-37.
-37?
Sorry, gentlemen. Kids being kids.
It’s okay.
No worries, Ma’am.
So soft.
Who are you seeing?
A family member.
-Kids being kids.
-Yes, Ma'am.
Hey, stop!
Are you sure you want to change hospitals?
I’m sure.
Can you give this to that young man?
-Of course.
-Thank you, Nurse.
-Alam?
-What wrong?
Where are you going now?
-Nowhere to run.
-Gotcha!
Shut up. I don’t need to hear your shit.
-My wife’s pregnant.
-I want my collateral.
Where’s your car key?
Or give me that laptop!
Get out of the way!
Are you okay?
You woke up the beast!
Oh my God, what is she doing?
Don’t piss me off.
How dare you hit my son?
Easy, lady.
I’m here to ask him for collateral.
Where are his car keys?
Your son is deep in debt, you know that?
Give him the car keys, honey.
Just give him them.
The car is with Ivan.
-Hey, don’t start any trouble here.
-No trouble, Sir. Relax.
-Come with me.
-Hands off! I can walk by myself.
This is not over yet. I’m onto you!
Take them out, Sir.
Easy!
You parked the car at Ivan’s house?
Yes, honey.
You’re dealing with that loan shark again?
You promised me, Alam. You swore to me.
I know, honey.
What about that book deal?
Is that even real?
Let me explain.
This is a baby, Alam.
Not a wedding organizer who you can charm.
Not your Twitter followers.
This is a baby, Alam! It’s that simple.
Not a doll.
Won’t you let me explain?
What else to explain?
This is what you’re good at.
Making up excuses.
If I got a dictionary
and look up the word “excuses”,
I bet I’d find your face there!
Are you even telling the truth now?
Or is it more lies?
More deceit?
I’m sorry.
Get out. Get out!
Get out!
Easy, child.
Come. Come.
Just lie down.
-It hurts.
-It's okay.
-Nurse.
-Yes, Ma’am?
CALLING ERIK
Well?
Hello, Erik. How many people do you need?
You have any bail plan?
Where’s your post? What kind of exit plan?
And my fee excludes meal.
Whoa, slow down. For a guy
who’s not a player, you’re pretty savvy.
You slow down.
I may not be a capitalist like you,
but I know my stuff.
Keynes? Smith? Who else?
Okay, let me check about your questions.
For details.
I’ll let you know.
But make sure you provide the crowd.
-Make sure you transfer my money first.
-Consider it done.
Got it, bro.
I’ll bring my crowd and the equipment.
I got another demonstration next week.
Will you be my guy?
At the district court.
They ask for grassroots crowd.
So you finally got realistic now?
The baby’s got power over you.
All right, I’ll be right there.
Room 3310, right? Yes, Ma’am. Thank you.
Mr. Alam! I was just looking for you.
I wanted to give you this, from Mrs. Dian.
Who’s Mrs. Dian?
You went to her room by mistake earlier?
But, sorry, I kind of read the letter.
She thanks you for
reminding her about responsibility.
That’s about it.
I have to go see a patient.
Nurse?
Just pray for everything.
So, Mrs. Dian has moved
to a clinic nearby.
So she can save some money.
She changed her mind because of you.
She’s done worrying
about what her neighbors say.
About her husband not being here.
That’s why she came
to this hospital in the first place.
For more prestige.
Hey, hold it up.
I also learned a lot from you, by the way.
When you tweeted about online cabs?
My husband didn’t join
the demonstration because of it.
See, your tweets made a difference.
I need to check this.
-Here.
-Just a minute.
What’s your bank account number?
Mia, everything is meant to be.
It’s your destiny to have
that boy as your husband.
What can you do?
You have to be the stronger one.
When the baby’s here,
you can stay at our house.
With your dad and me.
And the baby. All of us together.
I can help take care of the baby.
I’ll help you out.
Yes, Mom.
I’m good with babies.
I’ll do it at your house.
Yes, Mom.
You still have your room at our house.
You can stay there.
We’ll change the sheets and everything.
YOUR BANK ACCOUNT NUMBER?
I’LL TRANSFER THE MONEY NOW.
The usual.
Try some.
I’ve always wanted to taste one of these.
Those foreign contractors like them.
What’s wrong? You look a mess.
My wife’s about to give birth.
Your first?
Just like Marno.
My crane operator who had the accident.
Three days, working overtime, no sleep.
He’s with his baby now,
but he’s hospitalized.
He missed out on the birth.
Because of the accident,
we can’t lift our stuff up.
No other crane operators are available.
We have the money.
400 bucks isn't bad, right?
Jakarta is full
of construction right now.
Everybody’s busy.
Sorry, I’m rambling.
Are you having a boy or a girl?
We don’t know yet.
You like surprises, huh?
Whether it’s a boy or a girl,
it’ll be proud of you.
Its dad can manage.
He’s there when it arrives.
What was that you say?
About the 400 bucks?
The 400 bucks.
-Yes?
-Have you got your guy?
-Excuse me.
-Good evening.
Hi, Doctor.
How’s everything?
How is her condition?
It must already be dilation eight.
But I think it’s stuck.
Mrs. Mia has also lost her energy.
We don’t want that.
-Doctor?
-Yes?
Can I still have a normal birth?
It’s easy to do something about the pain.
But you have to keep your spirits up,
and have faith in yourself,
believe you can do it.
I’ll be right here to help. Okay?
You can do it, Mrs. Mia.
Who would’ve thought?
My random rambling
has found me a replacement.
You’ve operated this type before, right?
Yes, when I was in Dubai.
Thank God. This is great news.
Come on, man.
-All good?
-It’s ready.
Hey, man, thanks for doing this.
Otherwise we won’t get our pay.
Thanks so much, man!
-Thank you, man!
-You’re welcome.
We really appreciate it!
Come on, hurry up.
Those dealing with the crane,
take your position.
Come on.
Shit, this is high.
Okay, Dubai Schmubai! Fuck it.
Alam, are you okay there?
What’s taking so long?
Can you operate it or not?
Relax. I’m saying a little prayer.
Oh, okay.
Something wrong? Why so unsteady?
Alam? Are you still alive?
I’m getting to know this baby.
It’s different than the one in Dubai.
Okay.
It's Nugraha, Faisal’s lawyer.
Where do I send the lawsuit?
To the hospital or where?
To the left, Alam. Left.
Steady. Hold it.
Swing left, slowly.
Yes, swing right slowly.
Forward, Alam, forward.
Hold it. Smoothly now.
Almost there. Get it down.
It’s getting there. Down. Down.
Take it down now.
Easy.
Go on. Smoothly.
Come on, man. Yes.
Yes, okay. We got it!
I’m sorry.
I can only pay you 200 bucks.
We used half of the money
for Marno’s hospital admission.
Hey, the helmet!
-Mia! Honey!
-Alam.
Mia!
-Mia honey!
-Alam!
Honey, you can have a normal birth.
I’ve bought the N2O tube.
You can ask the nurse what it’s for.
It’s for normal births, honey.
I’m sure a thousand percent
you can give birth normally.
A thousand percent!
You’ve got to have your normal birth.
-Sir, this is as far as you can go.
-Please wait here.
That’s my husband.
Nurse, explain about the N2O. Nurse!
Yes, I know, but your husband can’t go in.
for hygiene reasons.
What was he talking about?
The N2O will make you more relaxed.
It makes the process easier for you. Okay?
Please.
Mrs. Mia Ayudia, listen to me carefully.
When I say inhale, you inhale.
When I say push, you push.
Now take a deep inhale.
Okay. Now push!
Push!
Open your eyes. Look at your stomach.
Come on, Ma'am.
-More. A little more.
-Come on.
Easy, Ma’am. Just relax, okay.
-Hold.
-Ready? On my count.
Push, push. Harder. Harder.
Open your eyes.
Push, push harder.
Keep pushing, Ma'am.
Push, push.
Congratulations, Ma’am!
It's a scrappy boy!
Congratulations, Mr. Alam.
He’s a little champ.
Thank you, Doctor.
Dear! Dear!
Let’s always visit our grandson together.
We’ll have playdates.
Of course. Promise me.
Wear this.
For your future second grandchild!
Thank you.
You have a son now. Do the best for him.
You’re a father now.
For your son’s sake, do as I say.
Move to VIP!
My grandson!
You did me proud.
-I’m proud of you, Ma.
-I'm proud of you.
I’m proud of you, son.
MRS. MIA AND MR. ALAM TANJUNG
My life.
I would like to publicly apologize
to @faisalPTA
and withdraw all my statements.
Let’s all be rational adults.
Look at you.
I’ll see you soon.
Amrin, this is my son.
Amrin, you’re an uncle now.
Praise God. Is Mia okay? Is your son okay?
Praise God, everybody’s healthy.
Amrin, let’s meet up. Our usual place?