This is my dad, Choi Cho-jin,
also known as Tyo Anggara.
And this was his aspiration.
When will you pay your debts?
I have no money.
That's the wrong concept in Indonesia,
you send a debt collector to poor people,
even the boss pays a visit.
Poor people should receive charity,
not threats.
So can I borrow some more?
That's what he wanted to be.
But he ended up like this.
"Those who are afraid to ask,
speak the loudest."
Sir, lower the price some more.
I brought my own sack.
No way!
It's lower than the buying price.
You can take it or leave it.
Dad didn't finish his school
but learned trading at the market.
So that's how you do it?
Do you buy it now, and then sell it
during Eid al-Fitr?
-With an increased price?
-Yes.
It's cheaper when you buy it now.
But it's more expensive
when you buy it later.
A merchant has to be smart
to gain more profit.
Gradually, Dad learned how to make dough.
Lower the price some more.
I brought my own sack.
Gosh!
"A frog trapped in ice."
It's lower than the buying price.
Finally, Dad made his dream come true.
To have his own store.
-Come on.
-No way!
-I'm a regular customer.
-No!
He kept collecting money.
Well done. You solved everything.
Yeni is such a smart student.
This is my mom, Yeni Huang.
Before she became Yeni Anggara, of course.
Forget it. Stop thinking about school.
I don't have the money.
You should take a sewing course.
-How much?
-One hundred.
What?
Did I hear you right?
Your price is too high!
How can rice be that pricey?
This is a difficult time.
Prices are going up. We're in a crisis.
Lower the price a little.
Please?
Let's make it 50.
Until Dad realized
that there was another kind of profit.
I'll tell you what.
I'm not lowering the price.
But I'll deliver this to your house.
To your doorstep.
To our house.
That sack he delivered
brought them closer.
This was the old generation.
Where you could gain a new friend
with just a sack.
Let's take pictures.
Perhaps since they both
couldn't finish school,
they ended up getting married.
For dowry, Dad promised Mom
a house plus a shop or a shophouse.
-The most luxurious one in Jakarta.
-Smile!
Look happy!
Let me take a shot. This is good.
One, two... Goodness!
Ma'am, stop shaking their hands!
Hurry! I'm running out of film!
Hey, man!
Look happier!
That's good.
Ready? Goodness!
Miss!
Can't you see I'm working here?
Ma'am, stop shaking their hands!
Come on, look happy!
Yes, good!
Oh, gosh!
Damn! These people.
Okay, get ready. Look this way.
One, two...
One is a merchant,
while the other is good at math.
To fulfill his dream of becoming
a successful businessman,
they both agreed to put off having a baby.
Hey, Trisno, what are you doing?
His name is Huang Ang Jing.
The person I call A Shu.
Which means "Uncle", not something else.
PERFORMING ART FESTIVAL
HARAPAN BUANA HIGH SCHOOL
A Shu is the most "rock and roll" person
I've ever known.
It's like he never thinks of
anything else, even college or work.
He belongs to a generation
that grew up in the Reformation Era.
He's a cool guy, but...
See for yourself.
Quiet down!
Just stop singing!
Go run the store with your brother!
Your life will have more meaning!
Yes, okay, Ms. Dor!
Your voice is hideous!
-All right!
Get lost!
For years, the luxurious shop
was still out of reach.
But Mom got pregnant anyway.
It's like this, sir.
Your baby's position is not normal.
We need to do a C-section.
A C-section?
What?
A C-section, ma'am.
-What?
-A C-section!
Oh, inflation.
She's inflated because she is pregnant.
What's with this doctor?
Doctor, a C-section requires
a lot of extra money.
Goodness! No need!
I can still hold it, Doctor.
See, Doctor? My wife can still hold it.
I truly believe that your wife
can still hold it.
Yes, Doctor.
But I can't.
-What?
-What's wrong, Doctor?
If anything happens to your baby,
I will be responsible.
I can't stand to pay compensation.
-Doctor, can't you lower the price?
-Then I'll give you a second opinion.
Okay, tell us, Doctor.
We'll use a local suture thread.
What? Local?
What do you mean by a vocal lesson?
-Honey.
-What?
Local thread. Not a vocal lesson.
I see.
-There's one condition.
-What is it, Doctor?
She has to stitch it herself.
What? Goodness, Doctor!
I've never taken a sewing class!
I've told you to take a sewing course
and you refused!
We're not sewing shirts here!
Enough, it's not that.
Doctor, please lower the price some more.
-Look. Listen to me carefully.
-Yes.
-I will lower the price.
-Yes!
-There's one condition.
-What is that?
Impregnate your wife once again.
Come back here. I'll be your doctor again.
Deal?
-All right?
-Goodness!
-Right, thank you.
-Is he serious?
An ear, nose, and throat specialist
is next door.
Affordable! There's no need to haggle!
Excuse me.
Hurry up, please!
What did he say?
Get pregnant again!
What?
Your father-in-law can't do it anymore!
Not you! Our daughter!
-Hurry up, honey!
-Okay!
After fierce bargaining,
finally, I was born
with a C-section procedure.
Why is my grandson so quiet?
I can't hear his sound.
He's crying now, Mom.
Now what? Is there another problem?
It's like this, Doctor.
I want to give him an Indonesian name.
My father-in-law wants a Chinese name.
So that people will know his heritage.
But we were all born in Indonesia.
You all made a fuss about payment.
Now you're making a fuss
about free stuff like giving a name?
I'll name him.
-What?
-Do you have one?
-Of course.
Chuan Kee.
-What?
-Chuan Kee?
That's another Chinese name.
That's a food's name.
I'm just kidding.
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
Please forgive me.
Hey, what did he say?
Forgiven.
That's a good name, Kevin!
That doctor is smart.
Kevin?
Kevin Anggara, that's my name
on my birth certificate.
Born in the 2000s, people say
I belong to Generation Z.
Even more annoying than millennials.
They call us the MSG Generation.
That hurts! What's this?
MSG GENERATION? EASY GENERATION!
You cowards! All you do is criticize!
Hi!
-Vin, come down here!
-I will!
Eat first!
This is my brother.
He was born out of my dad's promise
to the doctor.
Honey, call your son.
Hey, watch it!
Vin, come down here! Eat first.
Later!
Hey, Vin, you know what?
I got this from my WhatsApp group.
Playing too many games
will make you stupid!
Ane gong!
I agree, Yeni.
Vin! Your mom got this
from her WhatsApp group.
Playing too many games
will make you stupid!
Ane gong.
Vin!
Why isn't this kid coming down?
Hey, come down here! Hurry!
Okay, all right!
Sir, I've brought everything down.
Hey, not all of them!
My son's not coming down yet!
No, honey.
We're unloading Haji Imron's bags order.
-Vin!
-Yes!
I'm hungry!
I'm not hungry yet.
You should stop playing games.
Sir, do you have that thing?
What thing?
You know, usually...
When I make a delivery,
I get that thing...
Oh, right.
I gave it to your boss.
So I don't get anything?
I've settled it already.
I even gave him some extra.
-Well then. Later, sir.
-Thanks.
I even rode a motorcycle here,
instead of walking.
Let's go, dear.
-Ready?
-Yes.
Good.
Come.
-Let's have a good meal once in a while.
-Yes!
Tend to the store seriously.
Don't close it too soon.
Sometimes housewives come late at night
to buy sewing threads.
-There's no such thing.
-Hurry, honey.
This is Dad's shophouse.
But this is not what my mom dreamed of.
Tyo, you look so handsome.
Where are you going?
I've been handsome for a long time.
That's why I'm dressed up like this.
We're going to a wedding
at Haji Imron's place.
I see.
Yeni, look at these eggs
I just bought from you!
I broke one and a chick came out!
Impossible!
I inspect my eggs every day!
I'm sure they're good!
You didn't buy them here!
Where else did I buy them?
I want compensation!
-Impossible!
-Come on, dear. Just give it to her.
People say customers are king.
Moreover, she's our neighbor.
Just give it to her.
Great! A little compliment
gives you a big head.
When will you buy me a shophouse
at Pantai Indah Kapuk
if we keep giving compensation?
Come on, stop yelling.
The neighbors are listening. Enough.
Trisno, please compensate her.
-Yes, brother.
-Let's go now.
That habit of yours!
-Thank you, Tyo!
-Yes.
Give her three less.
Yes, Yeni.
What is it, miss?
Here, replace them all.
I bought one kilogram.
One kilogram? Are you mugging us?
It's true!
Tomorrow is a school day,
and I've come back to the routine.
Dad, Mom, I'm leaving.
Okay.
-Hey, study hard!
-I will.
Honey, tell your son to study hard.
Study hard, Vin.
I will!
Tell him not to chat too much.
Don't chat too much, Vin.
We paid good money for your tuition.
And all you do is play!
We paid good money for your tuition,
and all you do is play!
Honey, you shouldn't have repeated
that part! I was talking to myself!
-Really!
-Yes, I knew that.
No problem.
Dad, Mom, I'm leaving.
-Okay!
-Okay, take care!
Vin!
This is Chelsea. My childhood friend.
How about it? Are you excited?
What? What's happening?
What's with you?
This is our first and last day--
You mean our first day of school
in our last year of school?
Yes, that's what I meant.
So how is it? What do you prepare?
Nothing, the usual.
We're not like freshmen
who have to prepare everything.
What's with you?
At least prepare something.
Morning, Ms. Chelsea, Mr. Kevin.
Morning, sir. We're over here.
Sorry.
-Okay then, sir.
-Stay in school, okay?
Don't use your tuition money for drugs.
Or those needle things.
Or...
Like that.
Take care!
I believe you'll be awarded
the best speaker this year.
For the English debate?
Wish me luck. This is my last chance.
I did. My guesses are always right.
Chelsea's a smart girl.
She never uses subtitles
while watching western movies.
Her childhood dream
is to become an ambassador.
I hope by the end of the year
I can get closer to her.
Morning, sir.
Wait! Who are you?
A teacher.
A teacher?
Yes.
A temporary one.
Oh, a temporary teacher?
-Are you new?
-Yes.
-Please go inside, sir.
-Okay.
Chelsea!
Bon-bon?
Goodness, I miss you so much!
-Chelsea!
-Hi, Bon!
How was your holiday?
Yes, it was fun.
This is Bon-Bon, my friend.
He actually knows a lot of things.
But well...
Did you guys see my Instagram story?
That's not how you spell Sydney.
Nobody reminded me, Kev.
I have gifts for you two.
Really? It's weird for you to remember.
Gosh, how cute, Bon. Thanks.
What's this?
That's candy with...
Koala poop flavor.
It's the tastiest
and it's a best-seller at the store.
It's fine. Maybe it's delicious.
Right. Thank you.
Okay. Let's go inside.
Come on.
While I was there,
I really missed Indonesian food.
-True, Indonesian food.
-Of course.
Padang rice, chicken satay.
Awesome.
I'm going to my class. Okay?
-Bye.
-Bye, Chel.
Hi, Jo.
-Hi, Chels.
-Bye.
Johana!
So?
This is Johana. Her voice is loud.
But that doesn't mean she's mean.
She's useful to Bon-bon.
Where's the gift for me?
Oh, right. I forgot. I'm sorry.
What's with you?
I reminded you, but you forgot me!
I know. Tomorrow, okay?
You're all talk!
Hey, Vin. Where's the Old Guy?
Last time I saw him
unboxing Blackpink's new cassette,
staring at Park Seung-il's photos,
covered SNSD's music video,
and got burnt from eating Samyang.
I forgot to tell you something.
When I'm suddenly asked like this
my mind just pours out.
Remind me.
Isn't "samyang" the Korean word
for "pooping"?
Samyang is when you know someone
you will "samyang."
That's "sayang." I know that one.
Friends!
Did you miss Dimas oppa?
This is the one they call "Old Guy."
His name is Dimas.
But he prefers to be called "oppa."
-Dimas!
How are you?
Dimas Prasetya.
Here.
Your names are difficult.
I can't memorize them.
Johana?
Here, sir.
Kevin?
Yes.
Bon-Bon?
Here, sir.
I just don't understand this class.
Of all students, only the four of you
are interested in science class.
As the school treasurer,
I sometimes wonder.
Why can't you just move
to the social class?
We can cut the budget.
Moreover, we just recently
recruited a new temporary teacher.
Hey, you.
The smart one. Please answer.
I think if we are transferred
to the social class,
this class will be empty
and occupied by scary creatures
that can be used
by Indonesian producers in movies
to rule the box office in Indonesia.
If that's the case, our cinemas
will be filled with horror movies, sir.
Why are we talking about horror movies?
Of course not, sir.
We just chose to be in science class.
Right, guys?
-That's right!
Hey, remind me.
What movie are we watching after school?
-Kafir!
Hey! Watch your language.
People might get offended.
Attention!
This is an important announcement.
I ask that all school activities
be ceased for the time being.
We haven't even started.
Right now, we are preparing
the prerequisites
for very important activity.
Which is...
"Super Student Cup."
And it will be held at our school.
I have also made an encouraging poster.
Which will be posted all over our school.
Thank you.
-Sir!
-Kafir!
In this new school year,
I will take your attendance.
Sir, you already did.
No, I didn't.
Aldo's channel keeps gaining followers.
He did this over the holiday.
His ketoprak unboxing video
became trending!
I know. That ketoprak unboxing
that he didn't even buy?
That video was no fun, Dim.
You better watch Uncle Hotman on holiday
In Bali.
Wait a minute. Remind me.
Is it Aldo or Hotman?
Aldo!
Hey!
Aldo?
If you keep bringing lunch boxes,
Mrs. Nia will be out of business.
Jo, remind me. Who is Mrs. Nia?
That's my part.
Who is Mrs. Nia?
Jo, remind me. Who is Mrs. Nia?
Our cafeteria lady!
Cafeteria lady, Mas.
Ma'am! Are you bankrupt?
Not yet.
Vin.
What are you doing?
Are you deaf? What are you doing?
When I'm wearing a headset,
that means I don't want to be disturbed.
Hey.
Is this your friend?
His channel has a lot of cute girls.
Yes, Aldo.
Finally, someone from our school
got famous.
If you put it that way,
some of our alumni became ministers.
Someone from last year's class won
the World Accounting Olympics.
Sheesh, Vin, I mean a real famous person.
A celebrity!
A YouTube celebrity?
Makes good vlogs, made into memes.
I mean someone who creates work, Vin!
This Aldo creates something.
Better than you,
playing games all the time.
No, Kev, let's have dinner!
On the way!
-Vin, your mom is calling!
-Just a second!
She'll be furious, then you'll get it.
Vin!
Viewers, the hoax spreading
is threatening our nation's unity.
-We're here.
-Hey, No.
Isn't that your friend?
The singer Syahrini is reported
to have suffered fractures
when she performed
her pretty back and forth moves.
Yes, brother.
Do you still talk about that?
Hey, Vin. Why is it so hard for me
to call you down for a meal?
You know my childhood was difficult.
We were poor!
We split one scrambled egg
for ten people, Vin!
I've been making meals like this every
day. And you're still not eating much!
The usual. When MSG Boy
sits in front of his computer
it will be hard to move him.
Hey! Excuse me?
I don't use MSG in my cooking.
Don't misunderstand, Yeni.
I'm not talking about MSG for food.
It's about Kevin's generation,
they want everything quick.
Everything is instant!
Well, he's not from your generation.
Your generation is a late bloomer.
-Late to get a job.
-Why me?
Late to get a girl, late to get married.
Everything's expired.
Why am I the target?
This is why I don't like being at home.
They call me lazy, MSG kid.
They don't even understand my world.
-Come on, let's eat.
-Let's eat.
Eat well.
Do your kicks at the futsal court.
What are you doing there?
Watching the moon?
There's nothing there.
Right there.
Why are you writing
while watching the moon?
Jakarta's moon is obstructed by smoke.
Give me a break, Vin.
I'm comfortable that way.
Just like you have to poop at home.
You know how uneasy it is for me
to sit where strangers' butts have been.
Don't be strangers then.
-Sir.
-Hi, sir.
Hi, sir, miss.
Let's not be strangers.
Hey, Vin. By the way...
You don't write blogs anymore, do you?
Your last post was two years ago.
Well, it's just like when you were a kid.
You couldn't sleep
until you listened to Joshua's songs.
Why don't you listen
to Joshua's songs anymore?
-Corny.
-There you go. Same with me.
-What was that, sir?
-Just a thief, sir.
Why aren't you chasing him?
According to the law,
my jurisdiction is from here to there.
The 03 Neighborhood Watch jurisdiction.
From here to there
is the 04 Neighborhood Watch jurisdiction.
Where did the thief go?
-To the 04.
-There you go.
But we just saw a security guard
chasing from 03 to 04.
That's Christopher,
he lives outside the law.
Okay then, sir, miss.
Carry on with your rendezvous.
LET'S HANG OUT. BRING KEVIN.
Dimas is asking us out. Come on.
There he is. Come on.
Dim!
Dimas.
-Hey, Chels, Kev!
-Hey!
Look!
World record! I'm so awesome!
I'll suggest you
to an Indonesian Record Museum.
What's with you, Vin? That was cool.
Thank you.
I thought we were going somewhere else.
I've told you.
This place is the most fun.
Can't you see my crowd? Make some noise!
Hey, by the way...
You guys should try this game.
-No!
-No, it's fine!
It's all right. Just a minute.
Noobs, really sorry.
But I don't think you'll be using
these machines tonight.
All these machines can only be used by me
and my guests.
Sheesh, uncle!
Take turns!
Did you call me "uncle"?
Call me...
Dimas oppa.
-Come on. Dimas oppa.
-Dimas oppa!
That's good.
Come on, oppa. It's our turn.
-Yes, Dim. We're leaving as well.
-No, it's all right.
Hey, cracker bits! Let me tell you,
I know all your shame, your sins!
Do you want me to report you?
Hey! You kid!
I know you always come here
when you skip classes!
You kid! I know you like to extort
your friends' money!
You kid...
You're not even a kid!
What are you doing here? Go home!
I'll report you!
What? You dare?
Friends,
the machines are ready. Let's go.
Vin, they're vacant.
Let's try them. It might be fun.
That's my girl!
Chel, are you serious? This corny game?
It's embarrassing.
What do you mean it's corny?
You were never fun.
Fine, I'll try this game. Watch me, okay?
-Come on, Dim.
-Chel, let's go.
-Watch me, Vin!
-Come on!
-How to play?
-Try this song.
It seems that they're having fun.
But not for me.
-Here.
-Okay. Vin.
Follow the song. One, two...
Move your feet like this.
Dim, just a second.
-Vin!
-Yes.
Vin, why did you leave?
-It wasn't fun.
-Yes, it was.
Chel, nowadays, we play games in our room.
On our phones and laptops.
But that's not the point.
What's important is playing together.
I also play games together
with other people.
But you don't see them directly.
The point is I'm not alone.
You've never been fun.
-It's like that.
-Sir.
Yes, sir, miss.
Did you have a date?
It's Aldo.
Hello, Do.
We're going out tomorrow, right?
Okay. Vin, I'm going inside.
-Right.
-Thank you, Vin.
Okay, Do. See you tomorrow.
Aldo.
The border between 03 and 04 Neighborhood
is such a fine line.
So if there's a thief running
from there to here,
we only have the right
to chase him up to here.
Do not cross the line.
Do you understand, Christopher?
Why are you shaking your head?
Goodness.
This guy just doesn't get it.
Come on. Let's eat chicken noodles.
The seller is in the 04 Neighborhood.
But he's not a thief!
Consume! Eat!
I said "eat", you understand very well!
Let's go!
There, you can see it for yourselves.
How boring my final school year is.
Accused of being an MSG kid,
having a lame friend,
and Chelsea getting closer with Aldo.
"Challenges to reaching your dream.
Clear all challenges. Win your points.
Studentrebelguide.com."
This guy is serious.
STUDENT REBEL GUIDE
ARE YOU FED UP WITH YOUR LIFE?
SCHOOL, SOCIAL LIFE, TV ETC
IS YOUR LIFE EMPTY? SIGN IN
This is it. I think this website
will make my school year interesting.
Go on, easy.
That's it. Hold it.
READY TO HOST THE SUPER STUDENT CUP XX
My poop just went back up.
It's Mr. Rustam's face all over.
If I take one down, will he get mad?
The distance between City A and City B
is 3,800 kilometers.
Mr. Margono
filled his gas tank
for 60 liters.
His head fell off!
Ghost!
You're going to hell, Kev.
Come on, Kevin. Get real.
-Here!
-Where?
-Here! This kid, his head fell off!
What? No, his head is still there, sir.
Somebody lost his head?
That's right, sir.
Maybe you didn't see it right.
This teacher, sometimes he daydreams.
Gosh.
My heart almost stopped.
What should we do?
My heart...
Come on, sir. Get some rest.
His heart, dude!
Your prank is lethal, man!
You're insane, Kev.
I'm not looking. His face is so funny.
With this, I will ask my classmates
to do exciting stuff.
Without them knowing about this website.
Marjuki.
Temporary Teacher.
What the heck? Why is it green?
If I was the headmaster,
it wouldn't be like this.
You know the bureaucracy, right?
Where's the video?
He's mad at the chicken seller?
Oh, he's buying chicken noodles.
-Hi, guys.
-Hi, everyone!
Somebody's asking a question.
From Qbayunaughty007.
I remember him well.
He's an Aldolisius member from Tangerang.
What are we looking at?
The future.
Be quiet.
Trust me.
Lately, there have been
some people inserting letters,
flowers, food, all kinds of stuff
into my locker.
Maybe it was you, Cin?
Will this take long?
I feel like throwing up looking at him!
Throw up? Morning sickness?
Perhaps it was you, Chel?
-Three, two, one!
-Two, one!
I take it back.
Turns out that the last school year
can be fun.
Not just for me,
but for my friends as well.
This is out of line, sir.
I wouldn't draw you this ugly, sir.
Mr. Tito.
Gather all the teachers in my office.
Mr. Juki.
Your office or your office?
I mean the headmaster's office.
I see. Okay, sir.
Where did you find that temporary teacher?
Sorry, sir. I found him on the Internet.
Are these all the teachers you can find?
Sorry, sir. But the other teachers have
ongoing classes.
Where's Mr. Bambang?
Mr. Bambang has
an overlapping schedule, sir.
Overlapping?
He has to go withdraw our salary.
Thank goodness.
Your salary is included.
That's good. All right.
Hey, get my mic.
Mr. Juki. Please get my mic.
Your mic or your mic?
I mean Mr. Headmaster's mic.
Here you go, sir.
-What is this?
-Your mic, sir.
-Put it there!
-Oh, right.
You amateur!
Next time, don't use an application
to hire a temporary teacher.
Yes, sir.
Listen carefully!
Attention to all teachers!
The poster at the front gate,
whose picture is that?
-Yours.
Before it was vandalized, sir.
It is proven that there are so many people
who envy my success!
I ask you all
that poster in front of our school
to be replaced with a new one.
Yes, sir.
What?
Who's going to remind me if nobody's here?
So...
How are things?
What about the event's cost?
How about money from Luna, sir?
Right, that's...
That goes into my pocket.
Yes.
Soon I will retire.
Where else can I get my income?
Yes.
That can be arranged.
Yes. Right, thank you.
Who's there?
From that phone conversation,
I suspect our headmaster is up to no good.
You shouldn't be prejudiced.
It may become a slander.
Then what was that about?
He talked about money,
retirement, and how it's hard
to get income.
No wonder he's so eager
for this cup event.
-Perhaps...
-Graft.
I have to tell this to Uncle Hotman.
From now on, we have a new goal.
Exposing dishonesties in this school.
Awesome. Like that movie,
Catatan Akhir Sekolah?
-I'll be Vino G. Bastian.
-What year was that?
Hey!
What are you doing there?
-Are you smoking?
-No!
-What?
-No.
What are you doing?
Science class is that way.
Let's get to know each other. High five.
High five, my foot!
Well, well.
A luxurious car delivery.
My students sure are rich.
For goodness sake!
Oh, my. Is that a new car, sir?
Did you buy it online?
Make an unboxing video, sir.
Come on, Leo. Let's swim some more.
I sell good eggs, ma'am.
Javanese chicken. They live a happy life.
How much do you want?
Yeni, I'm leaving.
You're dressed up nicely for a Saturday.
Where are you going?
The church.
What? Church?
Yes, so what?
Uncle, you converted?
No, Vin.
A friend asked me to sing at her church.
Dad, is that okay?
It's okay.
It's all right.
When you help people,
don't discriminate against their religion.
What's important is your good intentions,
don't differentiate people.
You know what they say.
Teachers pee standing.
Students pee all over.
Right, dear?
Yes, that's right, Vin.
Just listen to your dad.
See? Right?
It's not every day that I agree with you.
Help your dad.
I'm going, brother.
-Yes, take care, No.
-Okay.
Vin, help me take this stuff
to Mr. Haji's place.
What? I have to attend an event at school.
Vin, it's a Saturday.
It's just an extracurricular activity.
It won't take long, okay?
-Is it still far, Dad?
-Relax, Vin.
Five more turns.
Three left, two right.
Why can't we use a map?
Gosh, Vin.
Do you think if we use a map
we can get there instantly?
No, right?
Do it like this. I know the way.
Then why can't you send a courier?
Why must we deliver it ourselves?
You'll see why I want
to make a delivery myself.
-Here you go, Mr. Haji.
-Gosh.
My congregation will love this.
-Yes.
-The quality of your bags...
Like this.
You're too kind, Mr. Haji.
Mr. Haji.
I made these special for you.
Special.
Twenty-five percent discount.
But don't tell anyone, Mr. Haji.
Then I'll order 300 pieces.
This is 300.
We complete each other, huh?
Come on, Dim.
Just stir it up. Do it right.
Count them first, Mr. Haji.
Anggara, I've been your customer
for a long time.
-No need for that.
-Just in case.
Dad, I unloaded them all.
-Done?
-Yes.
You got everything?
Is this your kid?
-Yes, my kid.
-Goodness.
That's good. A son helping his father.
Don't be ashamed, don't be embarrassed.
Because embarrassment is more dangerous
than the embargo.
Listen to him, Kevin.
Well, you know how kids are.
Just as they say, when a tree falls,
the fruits fall,
not far from the boat, sir.
I don't get it.
I swear I don't get it.
Like father, like son.
Oh, right.
This...
Whose this?
-It's yours.
-Oh, right.
Vin...
Is your school still far away?
Five more turns.
Three to the left, two to the right.
That's why you should take me to school
once in a while.
Yes. I want that as well.
But I'm busy with lots of work.
Like today, for example.
I had to make a delivery.
But Dad,
do you usually give discounts like that?
What if Mom finds out?
Look, Vin.
In business,
we don't need profits all the time.
But we also need blessings.
Like what I did.
I'm sure Mr. Haji will pray
for my business.
Profits are important.
But we have to be honest.
We must not cheat
and be mean just to gain something.
-Remember that, okay?
-Yes, Dad.
So how's your day?
It's great, thank you for asking.
How about you?
Yes, I'm doing well. I guess.
I'm fine. Have you studied English?
Cause we have a lot to study...
I'm looking at Cindy and Chelsea.
I thought it was Aldo.
Enough.
Hurry, stir it up. Hey!
-Jo, we're going.
-Come on.
Kevin will catch up with us.
This will get ruined!
Come on!
I'll get off up front, Dad. It's close.
-Which way?
-Up front.
Remind me.
Why are we here?
-You got caught!
You're lucky my expensive bag
didn't get stained.
Had it gotten dirty,
can you three afford to pay for it?
It's a knock off.
If I make this go viral,
you're all finished.
Chel.
Vin, what's with your friends?
They tried to pour this stuff
onto the English Club members.
You know how much the English Club
means to me, Vin!
They were looking
for Doraemon's magic pocket
and helped the Monkey King
to find the scriptures
and help Naruto to defeat Madara
to become a Hokage.
I'll explain later.
Why not now? We're all here.
This is our club activity.
What club?
Nasojel Club.
Remind me.
What's "Nasojel"?
People who eat...
People who love long gel.
National Society
of Jelly Enthusiasts Club.
There!
Wait. National Society
of Jelly Enthusiasts Club?
Truly, seance students are weird.
-Science.
Yes, that's what I meant.
Don't correct me.
Enough. I don't understand this.
Don't try this again. Clean everything.
Chel.
Fine, if Chelsea said so.
Wait.
What about my expensive bag?
-It's a knock off!
Chel.
What?
Look. Actually, I started all this.
They only tagged along because it was fun.
What I didn't tell you is that
we are accepting prank challenges
from a website.
Website? You didn't tell me about it.
Now you're putting our lives at risk?
Yes, sorry.
A few days back,
I found this website,
studentrebelguide.com.
This website's like a game.
There are challenges.
Wait a minute.
A person like you
did silly stuff like this
just because of an internet challenge?
But I tried to cancel it, Chel.
I texted you.
They want to hurry!
-What should I do?
-Enough.
I'll go grab my bag. I'm going home.
Okay, I'm sorry.
But we have a new purpose now.
To expose...
Graft practice.
Oh, right.
But I'm still playing
as Vino G. Bastian, period.
I'm going to grab my bag
and go after Chelsea.
-What?
-Hey, what about Vino?
Wait a second. Dim, Jo, remind me.
What is all this?
Student Rebel? Graft practice?
Vino Bas...
Vino, he was in the movie
Catatan Akhir Sekolah.
Who was the star? Iqbal Ramadhan?
Vino.
-Vino Ramadhan?
-Vino G. Bastian!
Chel.
Chelsea.
-Chel.
-Vin.
What's with you? You're so noisy!
I want to apologize.
Vin.
I want you to stop doing those challenges!
I just can't understand.
Why did you get carried away
with stuff like this?
Didn't you tell me to keep a high spirit
for this last school year?
Oh, so it's my fault?
No.
Relax, you won't become a victim.
Why shouldn't I?
Why don't you make me a victim as well?
What's so special about me?
Because I consider you as my...
Like my PS1 that I used to play at home,
and then my parents scolded me.
You're weird.
Chel! Chelsea!
Chel!
Thank you so much for singing
at my church event.
You're welcome.
Hey, what made you decide to ask me?
Because I remember that during high school
you had a great voice.
-Right?
-Do you remember that?
But... No, I'm curious.
Why didn't you use this talent of yours?
Well...
If only I was certain about my dreams,
there wouldn't be songs like
Everything
Is because of love
-Okay.
-Like that.
Yes, you have a great voice.
-I do, right?
-Yes.
Don't embarrass us.
But no, your voice is great.
Really, it's great.
I make you ashamed.
Yes.
But you missed me, right?
Well, I mean...
It makes you miss me... No, I mean...
It reminds you...
Yes.
-Come, eat these.
-Okay.
Jo!
-Sir, take Lady to her stable.
-Okay.
Be patient!
If I don't feed Grandpa's horse,
it wants to return to the Netherlands.
Guys, we'll stop doing pranks for a week.
What? Why?
-Aren't you the most enthusiastic?
-Yes, I've been staring at this website.
You guys are insensitive.
This clearly has something to do
with Chelsea.
-No!
-Really?
If you ask me,
you two are like Song Hye-kyo
and Song Joong-ki.
So adorable.
Remind me, Jo.
Who's Romeo and Juliet?
What Romeo and Juliet?
Song Hye-kyo and Song Joong-ki.
Right. Song Joong-ki and Song Song Song.
How should I know? You think I'm a Song...
Writer?
Enough!
We stopped doing pranks
not because of Chelsea,
but because we're preparing
for a bigger prank.
-Really?
Yes, take a look.
Mr. Margono...
Finally, that day came.
I will expose all the dishonesties
in this school.
Received a delivery...
Which then...
-Be ready.
-Ready.
-Open the door.
Open the door.
-It's open, sir.
-The car!
Good day, gentlemen.
Mrs. Dibyo. Welcome to our school.
How was your trip?
Safe?
Actually, the trip wasn't very nice.
So my condition at this moment,
I don't have much time
because I'm meeting RI 3.
-Don't you mean RI 2?
-Three.
All right.
-Let's get started, ma'am.
-Yes.
-Let's observe the activities...
-Sure.
Can you please clean up this walkway?
Of course, right away.
Right.
Four thousand rupiah per kilogram.
How much
will his profit be?
Please come in, ma'am.
Good day.
-Good day to you all.
-Good day, sir.
-Operational cost...
-Ma'am.
Mrs. Dibyo, we should allow
this teaching process...
in progress, ma'am. Just let him be.
He's concentrating.
Okay.
It's so crowded.
How come there are only four of them?
Are the others skipping class?
No, ma'am. They're not skipping class.
This is the science class.
It only has four students.
These four are the best, ma'am.
So we facilitate them.
We prepared this class for them.
Do you get it?
I do.
Right. That's right.
What's with that one in the back,
wearing a headband?
Do you have a headache?
Are the lessons too difficult?
Or maybe you can't keep up
with this class?
Yes.
But that kid looks a bit...
Old.
Oh, no. He's not old.
He's just a kid.
But he does look a bit older.
It's understandable.
Kids nowadays look older than their age.
Now let us check...
Our toilets and tribunes.
Oh, yes. Fine.
-Please, this way.
-Tribunes...
Just a second, sir.
Right. Carry on.
Let's move on.
About our water,
we produce our own here from a well.
So the participants don't need to worry
about water shortage.
Everything is under control.
Oh, okay.
Shall we inspect it, ma'am?
I can't.
-I apologize, ma'am. I didn't realize.
-It's okay.
Mr. Bambang,
please demonstrate our waterworks.
Mr. Juki. Demonstrate it.
Yes, sir.
Goodness! What's with you?
Telling that temporary teacher to do it?
I don't trust him.
-Go with him.
-Okay, sir.
I don't trust him either. Please.
Yes, ma'am.
-Hold this.
-Yes.
-Amazing!
-Such strong pressure, ma'am.
Here it is, ma'am.
About our sports field...
The size of our school field
is very much ideal.
It follows international caliber.
And the size is extraordinary.
That tribune...
People can sit on it, right?
Oh, about that tribune...
It's under the process
of being repaired...
It's possible. Why not?
Let's try it.
-Mr. Bambang!
-Yes, sir?
Please test the tribune, all right?
Mr. Juki.
Check the tribune.
-Me?
-Yes.
-Right, sir.
-Stop asking Juki!
Both of you!
Yes, sir. Ready.
Mr. No!
Go with them. I don't trust them.
Yes, ma'am.
Jo, remind me.
Did I light the match or not?
What's with you?
It's safe, Mr. Juki.
-It's safe.
-It was built using the proper funds.
I wouldn't embezzle it.
Get off!
What is he saying?
I think he's telling you to step down
from your position as the headmaster.
Get off!
Vin!
-Vin!
-Who told you to lay down there?
Sorry! My firecrackers!
I think, based on what I see
I have to give it a second thought.
It seems impossible for this school
to organize...
Club... What's its name?
-Super Student Cup, ma'am.
-Right.
I think it's impossible.
-I...
-Okay, thank you.
Actually, I...
I'm sure all parents here already know
why I gathered you in this room.
This incident is so heartbreaking!
All thanks to your children
who have committed a brutal act!
Such a mess!
Excuse me, sir.
Yes, what is it?
I'm Baris Napitupulu
asking permission
to speak privately with Jo.
Yes, go ahead.
I...
came all the way
from the border of our country!
Now I'm at the border of my emotions!
Your attitude is embarrassing...
Me!
Do you understand?
I spent all my money
on your school tuition!
And you caused trouble?
What's with this kid?
You humiliate me.
I've never done
anything like this in my life.
Bon, remind Daddy.
Your grades are good this time, right?
They're good, Dad.
But this is not about that.
Sir, we all heard your phone conversation.
And we all suspect
that you're committing graft practice.
That's why we tried to ruin the
Super Student Cup plan for this school,
to expose your crime!
Kevin!
What are you talking about?
Excuse me, sir.
I...
And you...
We are both servants of the country!
I maintain security!
You maintain education!
Don't let the headmaster turn into...
headless.
Death sentences for corrupt officials.
For goodness sake, sir!
Why can't you be a good role model?
This is an amazing achievement, Vin.
Bon, remind Daddy.
What are we here for?
Our headmaster committed corruption.
Corruption?
Sir! Corruption is my department!
I'm a lawyer for corrupt officials.
If I defend you
from the beginning to the end,
you will be acquitted of all charges.
Just relax, sir.
It's my reputation, sir!
For ten years,
I was the best headmaster!
I've never committed
any corruption offense.
We all heard your phone conversation.
You talked about money.
And how hard it's going to be
when you retire.
Right, guys?
That's right.
-Just admit it!
-We heard it!
-Admit it!
-I'll call Uncle Hotman.
Children, listen.
Our headmaster here
always craves achievement.
His narcissism can't be helped.
And he thinks he's so handsome.
A bit reckless.
But one thing I can say about Mr. Rustam
is that he is an honest man.
I agree!
Mr. Rustam never committed corruption!
Honest!
As the school treasurer,
I have valid data.
In fact, Mr. Rustam here
has been covering
the school's lack of funds.
I have the complete record.
We have the record, don't we, Mr. Tito?
Do you have the record, Mr. Juki?
Mr. Juki? Yes, sir. We have the record.
Excuse me, sir.
You!
Are embarrassing...
Me!
I almost turned the headmaster headless!
It would be better
if he's the head of a branch!
If I shoot one head,
he still has another branch!
Do you understand?
Truly, slandering is worse than killing!
You have to study seriously!
Our kind shouldn't mess around!
Bon, remind Daddy.
Who committed corruption?
-Nobody did, Dad.
-I see.
Enough! Stop all this!
All merits,
especially ones
I have done all this time...
There's no need to talk about them.
But there's punishment
for students who have committed
this brutal act!
I will give a suspension!
To you, you, you and you!
And Kevin,
I will give you more suspension!
A longer one.
That school tribune incident
was never in my plan.
Remind me, Jo. What blueprint is this?
This is the blueprint for our future home.
Suddenly I remembered
this is our school's blueprint.
I did plan to sabotage the evaluation day.
What, no punctuation?
Add an emoji or something.
Make it look friendly.
A colon and a bracket or something?
The Super Student Cup preparations
felt wrong from the start.
That's why I felt the need
to give a lesson.
Some of the sabotage worked.
Place this bucket on top.
Tie it to the door. When the door opens,
and Mr. Tito comes out--
Got you! Mr. Tito!
What's all the ruckus and calling my name?
Remind me, Jo. What are we doing?
You want to mop the floor.
She's right.
-I'll mop the floor.
-Get the mop.
That's good.
That's right.
Shake it, Bon. Don't be so stiff.
Okay, sir.
-Excuse me, sir.
-Hey, you.
Yes, sir?
Do you think
I'll look good as a headmaster?
You look good, sir.
Try this, sir.
Sounds good, sir. You look dignified.
-Dignified?
-I'm heading home, sir.
Go ahead.
Some plans ran smoothly.
Well, some failed.
Hey, who vandalized this?
I don't know.
And it's more attractive with punctuation.
It's more proper. We got caught.
We're screwed. I'm out.
Actually, I wanted to meet
the last challenge.
Create commotion throughout the school
with fireworks.
I asked you to take the box
behind the door.
It is a box for Chinese New Year delivery.
Bon, he asked you to bring that one.
And you brought this one.
What? He asked me
to bring this one, not that one.
This and that.
Why are we bringing firecrackers?
Relax.
Trust Bon-bon.
What are you afraid of? It's safe.
Sure. Can you please
clean up this walkway?
The entourage is here!
So you know the story.
Thanks to Bon-bon bringing a firecracker
instead of a sparkler.
A son like you gives me a headache.
I've told you so many times.
You have to study seriously!
Now you're suspended, I'm embarrassed!
Honey, give it a rest.
Let me talk to him.
Vin.
I'm sorry.
All this time, I never took you to school.
You know how it is.
I'm busy with the store.
Making deliveries here and there.
I'm not a rich guy.
This store is all I have, Vin.
Even my promise to your Mom,
to buy a shophouse at Pantai Indah Kapuk,
I haven't fulfilled it to this day.
I'm not like other Chinese people, Vin.
I won't force you to run this store.
You can be whatever you want.
You can be a doctor, an engineer.
If possible,
you can be a governor.
It's all right.
But what's important
is that you have to be somebody.
A good person. Honest and hardworking.
Don't achieve anything the instant way.
-Do you understand?
-Yes.
That was good, honey.
I like that. No proverbs.
Hello?
Excuse me.
Chel.
My mother asked me to buy some thread.
Thread...
We have some.
But... Just a second.
I need to talk to you.
What do you want to say?
You want to say that you're happy?
For making a bad memory
in our last school year?
Do you know?
Since you got suspended,
Bon-bon and Johana have been shunned.
Nobody cares about them.
And Dimas...
His parents are planning to transfer him.
One more thing, Vin.
This year, our school won't host
the Super Student Cup.
We're disheartened.
I hope it's true.
That our last year means a lot to you.
I'm done. I'm not buying your thread.
The store next door sells thread.
Thanks.
Vin.
What's with this kid?
When I was in high school,
I was naughty just like you.
No, I was worse.
Here.
I was a school band vocalist.
You know how girls are crazy
about band members?
The Handsome Brother.
For kids nowadays, I would be like...
a YouTuber.
If only I was sure in the path I chose,
there wouldn't be songs like
Everything
Is because of love
-Everything...
-Who's song is that?
Someone.
I wish I hadn't doubted her support.
I wouldn't have lost everything.
Isn't this Bella Fauzi, that presenter?
The point, Vin, is...
don't be like me.
Who lives with doubts.
Yes, Uncle. I understand.
Kids nowadays would say,
"Move on."
Just like my uncle
who had a passion for music,
I too used to love writing.
1ST PLACE WRITING CONTEST
Until I lost that spirit to write
because the society made me doubt myself.
-Lame!
-You suck!
-You nerd!
-MSG kid!
Affected by people's words,
I finally stopped writing.
Maybe it's time for me to return
to the world that I believe.
Doing what I'm good at.
So I can be honest and be myself.
Making mistakes in life
is not the end of everything.
What's important is to get back up.
How diligent, sitting in front
of the computer this early.
It's useless to just write, Vin.
It's meaningless
if you don't apply it in your life.
Have you moved on yourself?
Hey, whoever is reading this,
I just want to say, I'm fine.
Well, I broke my left arm.
But other than that, I'm perfectly well.
During my absence in writing,
a lot of things happened.
Bon.
Remind me, who are you?
Kevin!
With these, I forgive you.
Sincerely.
You miss your hometown
in the Netherlands, don't you?
It's hot in here, I know.
Unlike your hometown.
Cock a doodle doo!
That's a rooster!
Remind me, Jo.
What does a horse sound like?
How should I know? Ask my Grandpa's horse!
I don't speak Dutch!
What does a horse sound like?
Again.
You miss me, don't you?
Really...
That's okay, it's good.
-Peace be upon you.
-Dimas!
Excuse us!
May the peace and mercy of Allah
be with you as well!
What are you doing here?
You dare come here, looking for Dimas?
Dimas is here,
but I won't allow him to come out.
What has he been doing at school?
I've sold my cows, my farmland,
just to send my son to school!
And he fooled around!
Thanks to you, brats!
Jo, remind me. What language is this?
Kroya.
Korean.
Dimas is actually from Korea.
You got that?
We're here to apologize, ma'am.
Apologize?
Wait until Eid al-Fitr!
Gosh.
We have to fast for 30 days first?
Think before you act!
Mother, what are you doing?
I've topped up our internet data.
You can watch your Korean drama again.
-I can watch my movies again?
-Yes.
-It's connected?
-It is.
Good boy.
You should pray first.
-No problem.
-Yes.
I have to bribe her
with internet data, man.
-She's Korean?
-What do you think?
-Not really.
-Of course not.
How silly of you to trust that.
How can a face like this be Korean?
Your mom said she's Korean!
Kroya, near Cilacap!
Dim, we brought you something
so you can show your talent.
Jo, show him.
Ta-da!
Dance competition!
Dance competition?
-Yes!
-Dance competition?
Yes!
-Competition!
-Yes!
Dimas! The "screaming" is not working!
I can only see that round thing
turning and turning!
The picture won't come out!
You mean streaming?
"Screaming!"
-Yes, streaming.
-It's not working!
That's why you should pray first.
Watching Korean dramas every day.
Why are these brats...
-May peace be upon you, Kroya!
-And upon you too!
-What's with those brats?
-Maybe they have things to do.
Come on, "screaming."
How is your preparation? Good?
What room is this?
English Club.
Well, do you think everything is fine?
Chicken. Fried chicken. I'll buy you one.
WE CAN STILL BE THE WINNERS
I need you to make a cool vlog
for our school.
Your English sucks.
Okay, I'll help you.
I'll buy you fried chicken.
Guys, I have important information.
We are not the host!
But that doesn't mean
we can't be the winner!
Our high school still has hope!
Our high school still has...
I'm hoping to bring back
the students' spirit.
To pay for my mistakes.
-Come on, Chel.
-We can do this!
Aldo! Let me help you.
Forward without fear!
Our high school will be the winner!
-We can do it!
-Our high school will be the winner!
Guys, don't forget to share this video
as much as possible on Instagram! Okay?
Don't forget to subscribe
to my YouTube channel.
Our high school still has hope!
March on!
I get it.
Oh, my!
Guys, this is what I call an arena.
Do you think we can win?
Hey, Dim. This will be
a historical place for you.
Do you see those faces?
Those are the faces that you will defeat.
-Gosh.
-Hey, you!
Other dance competition participants!
You better give up!
Because my friend here will be the winner.
Go back to your mom's house!
What are you looking at?
Do you want us to beat you badly?
-Which one, Jo?
-That one!
Do you know who taught
Michael Jackson to dance?
-My friend over here!
-Lord Dimas!
Dimas from Korea!
-Let's get inside.
-Let's.
Come on, Dim.
Dim!
Hey, where are you going?
I can't! I want to go home!
I'm embarrassed in front of them!
See? When he's scared,
his Korean comes out.
We're in front of the gate. Why scared?
Your words are giving me stage fright!
We're supporting you!
But not like that! I'm getting cold feet!
Maybe I can only dance
in front of those kids!
Just imagine dancing
Easy for you to say!
You never dance every time I tell you to!
See? Come on, shake it!
-That wasn't bad.
-Come on, you can do it.
-Come on, Dim.
-Come on.
Dimas!
Keep it down.
Welcome to the 20th Super Student Cup!
Over the years,
this event has been sponsored
by our sweetest lady,
Mrs. Dibyo!
Our lovely audience,
this year will be different than the last.
This is 2018. Last year was 2017.
This year, we'll have
a lot of competitions.
We have wall climbing,
skateboarding, go-karting,
dancing, and a singing competition!
And most importantly,
we'll have an English debate!
Give a round of applause!
Let the games begin!
Gosh, they're all good.
Our school's score is falling behind.
MEDAL TABLE
Hey, relax. We still have Dimas.
Hey, man, why are you
putting pressure on me?
Dim, relax. You can do this.
Our school still has Chelsea
and her English Club.
-Bon, join the go-cart race.
-I can't drive.
You can do everything, Bon.
You just forget about it all this time.
-Is that true, Jo?
-Yes!
Jo, you can sing.
He...
-Not now!
In the competition.
-Sir, sign her up.
-On it.
Keep your spirits up!
Our school can do this!
Dimas!
You can do it!
This kid.
This "screaming" is so nice.
Smooth.
Hello, guys. For all...
Welcome to the Super Student Cup.
English debate!
Our debate contestants are
Harapan
Mrs. Ana
High School...
Buana!
"Mrs." is mom.
Mom is "Bu", "Ibu."
"Ana" is your school. So?
No problem! Yes!
And this is...
69...
High School!
You know SMU?
S is "I".
Mu, "You".
You and I.
And guys...
This is the topic for the debate.
What is your opinion
about your generation?
Gen Z!
Please welcome!
69 High School!
Harapan Buana High School!
Very, very good afternoon!
Yes!
In today's society,
we're labeled the "MSG Generation."
Maybe it's because we have everything
at our fingertips.
But if you do one mistake,
it will be recorded,
and affect our future.
A threat that didn't exist
in our previous generation.
We are not a perfect generation.
But like all the generations before us,
we will carry on and find our own way.
Welcome to our Singing Competition final!
I'm not the one
That you've always dreamed of
I'm not her who has everything
I've never hoped that our story
Can become beautiful
But there's one thing I need you for
Have you ever realized
Every tear that falls
Down my cheek
I'm not the one
That you've always dreamed of
I'm not her who has everything
I've never hoped that our story
Can become beautiful
But there's one thing I need you for...
The overall champion
for the 20th Super Student Cup is...
Harapan Buana High School!
My beloved students,
I am so proud of you.
Proud!
Yes!
Awesome!
You're all great students!
Honey, Mr. Haji Imran is here!
Stop putting Leo under the sun.
He'll get dark. Come on.
-Just a minute, sir.
-Yes.
Mr. Haji.
-How are you, sir?
-I'm good, thank goodness.
Yes.
Why do you have to come all the way here?
If you need any merchandise, just call me.
I just want to maintain our relationship.
Also, I want to hand you
this wedding invitation.
You're getting married again?
Share some tips with me, sir.
How to get married again.
What are you whispering about?
You want to get married again?
Mr. Haji, just so you know.
He promised me a shophouse
at Pantai Indah Kapuk.
Now I'm old and I still haven't gotten it.
-You dare get married again?
-Honey.
The one getting married is Mr. Haji.
You old coot! Pervert!
Hey! Honey!
Don't repeat everything I say!
No!
Check who the groom is.
Read it. Imran Jr.
Imron Junior.
I'm Imron A. Imron Aja.
See, honey?
The one getting married is his junior.
My son.
We're sorry, Mr. Haji. Sorry.
Sorry.
Sir.
Kevin.
Sit.
What is it?
I wanted to help an old lady cross
the street and have lunch with you and--
Kevin.
You don't have to rush anything.
Take it slow.
What is it?
I want to apologize, sir.
Kevin.
I forgave you already.
And I've read your writings.
It's good.
Keep writing.
Be more detailed.
Be more specific.
I'm sure it will turn out well.
Okay?
Thank you, sir.
Okay.
Kevin.
Yes, sir?
One more thing.
If you do everything sincerely,
you will be successful.
Thank you, sir.
Luna.
I'm coming.
Vin, how's our final year?
Impressive.
Come on, let's take the picture!
I spent five years in high school
just for this picture, come on.
-What took so long?
-It's like waiting for the bus.
Jo, remind me.
What are we doing?
-Family picture, Bon!
Bon.
Remind Daddy. Whose parent is this?
Hey, man!
That thing.
I haven't got any.
-Oh, no.
-Dang!
It's that thing guy again!
For goodness sake!
Hey, what's with his thing?
That thing...
He didn't give me his thing.
Excuse me, everyone.
Can we just get on with it?
Take...
The picture!
#HIGHSCHOOLGRADUATION
School is finally over.
While I waited for college,
I cleaned up my blog
and posted my absurd stories at school.
Wait a minute!
I win!
In his retirement,
the headmaster became
the head of National Zebra Dove Lovers.
Well, wherever he is,
he's always becoming a leader.
Luna.
#WINNINGBIRD
Somebody moved on.
You?
Everything
Is because of love
A publisher was interested in my stories.
My writings were made into a book.
Finally, my book got published.
If you want to buy one, go to a bookstore.
The cover is yellow.
Pay at the cashier. Great!
How convenient. Reading books.
It's as if you own them,
but you're not buying them.
Just like a library.
Honey, it's all right.
Let them be.
Just consider it like this.
These kids are appreciating
our son's work.
Let them be?
If it stays like this, when will I get
that shophouse at Pantai Indah Kapuk?
Kevin's book...
How come there are no spaces
between the sentences?
You smarty pants!
You should get your eyes checked.
This book is awesome.
Just like what people say.
"A drop of stain
ruins the whole piggy bank."
You're weird.
Viewers, a syndicate of a hoax website
that has been operating for some time,
just recently got caught
by two security guards
in a crowded civilian area.
In their operation...
Vin.
This is Jes.
My high school friend who asked me
to sing in her church.
-Hi.
-I see.
So this is your reason to move on.
My uncle's so talented.
I know.
Your uncle should've been
as successful as...
Everything
Is because of love
Everything is because of love
But how?
Okay, so...
Since you've helped me with my church,
my fianc wants to ask you
to be a recording artist.
Come again?
My fianc wants to ask you
to be a recording artist.
Who's that?
What's with this kid?
Her fianc!
I mean, who's that singer?
Have you known her for a long time?
She's a high school friend.
-A high school friend?
-High school.
But I want to ask you something.
Was she this beautiful in high school?
She's beautiful.
Too bad she's engaged.
Everything
Is because of love
Everything is because of love
Chelsea.
Yes.
Hi, Mr. Kevin.
Sir, I'm here.
-What is it, sir?
-Why are you here?
I'm the security guard here.
Why are you at Chelsea's house?
Chelsea's house is within my jurisdiction.
That's why I'm standing by here.
Where's Chelsea?
Her parents took her to college
in Bandung.
You miss her, don't you?
This is the first time
I've lived far from Chelsea.
-There, there, Mr. Kevin.
-Sir, I'm here.
It doesn't feel good.
There, there, Mr. Kevin.
You can call her if you miss her.
Video call.
DM her on Instagram, right?
Yes, but you don't have to hug me.
I hugged you here,
you told me to face this way.
Now you're mad.
Sir, LDR is difficult.
Long-distance relationship.
Long means lengthy.
Distance means space.
Relationship means alliance.
Lengthy space liaison.
Is that a relationship or the Cipali toll?
But it doesn't matter.
I can always find an excuse
to go to Bandung at least once a month.
AT NIGHT I REMEMBER YOU, AT DAY I MISS YOU
DISTANCE IS ANNOYING
This is what I do when I'm alone.
I don't want to be a prankster anymore.
Hey, we have a new kid.
Hey, check his equipment.
You're so white, like cue stick chalk.
Hat.
Bag.
All right.
Yes, go ahead.
Wait.
Take one step backward.
Check his physique.
Let's see you squat.
Get up.
Squat.
Smile for your seniors.
There you go.
You're so handsome like Ernest.
Okay. Please continue.
Okay.
Hey, he called you.
Come back here.
Face that way.
No. Face this way.
Why do they call you Duck Mouth?
I got it when I was riding
the Kintoun Cloud to the Hogwarts School
while collecting the Infinity Stones
for 2019 Naruto as Hokage
with the help of Doraemon
and his Anywhere Door!
Well done!
-Well done, my foot!
-That is the right answer!
Repeat that to make it clear.
Repeat that. What did you say?
I got it when I was riding
the Kintoun Cloud to the Hogwarts School
while collecting the Infinity Stones
for 2019 Naruto as Hokage
with the help of Doraemon
and his Anywhere Door!
This is the one. Brilliant answer.
The Republic needs people like him.
People need people like you.
-Amen.
What? He was like...
What's your major here?
-Agriculture Literature!
-What?
-Is there such a thing?
-You haven't heard?
Explain it to him.
We do have
the Agriculture Literature Faculty.
They have their midterm test
at the village rice barn.
Lecturers come carrying rice plants.
There!
How can you not know?
What's your major?
I'm in the Vegetation Medicine Faculty.
What? You?
Civil Registration.
Veterinary Medicine! Civil Engineering!
Your faculties do not exist!
Yes, they do.
Sheesh.
What kind of campus is this?
I can't stand this place!
You're giving me a headache.
-Excuse me.
-Yes, go ahead.
I take it back.
Being a prankster is addictive.
-My parents scolded me...
-You're weird.
Chelsea.
-Chel!
-What?
-What is it, sir?
-He was talking to me.
Talking to you? He was talking to me!
He was facing me. Right, sir?
-Me.
-Me!
-You're so persistent!
-Ask the guy. Right, sir?
-You're not facing the right direction.
Right, sir?
Hey!
What are you kids doing?
-I bet you're smoking.
-What?
No, sir. No.
Come on, break it up!
Look. See?
Over the phone, he talked about money.
He's about to retire.
It will be hard.
Sorry!
This year...
Our school will not be the host...
Super... My god!
"Welcome" means "greeting."
"Goodbye" means "farewell."
The one who will win this thing
is surely not a squirrel!
This music is so jazzy.
-Follow my lead, ready?
-Yes!
Thank you, Australia!
And if I stand today
-Wrong lyrics, Delon!
-Oh, right.
Nobody's buying thread.
Let's close the store.
What's wrong?
Hey! Are you thieves?
Hey, this way.
What's wrong, man?
-Are you a thief?
-No, I own the store.
All thieves claim to be the owner
when they get caught!
Resisting an officer! Yellow card!
What is this, a soccer match?
-Come on!
-Annoying!
-Indeed.
-Hey!
-Are you his...
-Sir...
Are you his henchman?
He also owns the store, man.
Just a second.
-Trisno.
And this is Kevin.
Christopher, let's eat chicken.
I asked you out to eat!
Hey, Christopher!
-Excuse me, gentlemen.
-Yes, go ahead.
What? What's your major, huh?
-Hey, you two. Civil Registration?
-What's yours?