This is not
an Independence Day celebration
and I am not a dance instructor.
My name is Lastri,
I'm a freshman...
and this is my story.
Like every story,
there's always a beginning.
I'd like a refund for my plane ticket.
I don't want to change the date,
I want to cancel my flight. That's it.
My daughter can't go.
Where are you going, Mother?
I am going to campus.
You're applying as a student?
Yes.
Is there a problem?
But, ma'am...
What's your religion?
What does religion have to do with it?
Do you believe in God?
Yes, I do believe in God.
If you believe in God,
then you know that God
always listens to a mother's prayer.
You want me to pray good things for you,
or bad things?
We are going to take your picture.
Just act normal, ma'am.
UNIVERSITY CYBER INDONESIA
Alhamdulillah. Thank you God.
Thank you, thank you.
Welcome to Cyber Indonesia University.
This is a place where you
can be cool in your community
by saying,
"I am a Berdosa."
An abbreviation of Cyber Indonesia.
You only have one enemy.
That is the students of Institut Sains
Dan Pendidikan.
Or in short, Insap.
The Berdosas are enemies of the Insaps.
Stupid.
Look over here.
A millennial.
An attention seeking generation.
Miss, we were born between 1990-2000,
they call us
the post millennial generation.
You're the millennials.
Shut it!
What is this?
Why are you wearing a high school uniform?
You want to look cute,
you want to look like Gempi?
-What is Gempi?
-"What is Gempi?"
Why wear a costume like this?
Isn't this orientation?
Orientation? That's so old school.
Why did you wear a pan as a hat?
Dear God.
Why did you throw it?
You don't need that pan!
Are you also wearing a hairpiece?
-No.
-She is wearing a hairpiece.
-Just take it off!
-That hurts!
Take it off!
-Take it off.
-That hurts. Really.
This is her real hair.
Then, clean your make up.
Just clean your face.
Why do you want to look old?
This is my real look.
People want to look young.
Why do you want to look old?
-I am old.
-When were you born?
-Seventy years ago.
-What?
Please forgive me, Grandma.
I am really sorry.
Forgiven. Stop it. Come on, get up.
Grandma...
Are you really a grandmother?
-Of course.
-You remind me of my grandma.
You know...
My grandma is...
She is a grandmother.
Please forgive me, grandma.
I didn't mean it.
Grandma!
Hi, still with me, Danny Asolole.
Listen, there is a senior citizen
registered at Cyber Indonesia.
The wrinkles on her face are real.
Shut it!
Kak.
-What are you doing?
-Nothing.
Sandiaga Anu?
Sandiaga Uno.
I am a senior. So what if I say Anu?
Nothing, Kak.
This is your first day,
and yet, some of you are late.
You're university students.
You're no longer primary students,
that still need to be looked after
by your parents.
Do you understand?
Good morning.
I am really sorry, this is my daughter.
It might be important.
Whose mother is that?
She is one of the freshmen, Sir.
But she is old.
What is it, dear?
Can you turn off your cell phone, Grandma?
What?
You mean the pan? The small pan?
Yes, I brought it here, but...
Turn off the phone.
Okay, Sir. I have to go.
Let me introduce myself.
I am Chaerul Umam.
Welcome to Cyber Indonesia University.
-This morning...
-I have a question.
This is not a question and answer session.
Why was it named Cyber Indonesia?
Why don't you use Bahasa Indonesia?
That's too western.
We are trying to embrace
the Industrial Revolution 4.0.
So...
I am answering your question.
What is the Industrial Revolution 4.0?
I don't know anything about that.
How would I know
about Industrial Revolution 4.0?
That's why I asked him.
We shouldn't be afraid to ask questions.
You're right.
And what did the professor do?
He is not a professor. He is the dean.
That Chaerul really looks like
a puffer fish.
Maybe he is holding his anger against me.
-Mom?
-Yes?
Why did you put four plates on the table?
I couldn't help it.
Assalamualaikum.
Wa'alaikumsalam.
-Hi, Dear.
-Mas.
I am so hungry.
That fish looks so...
Here.
I cooked the fish with different
spices. Have a try.
Okay.
Good morning, Grandma.
Just call me Lastri.
Hi, Grandma.
Mr. Chaerul said hello.
Really?
Grandma.
Good morning, Grandma.
Good morning.
Just call me Lastri.
No, that's not polite.
I am the one asking you.
Come on, try calling me Lastri.
Good morning, Lastri.
Easy, right?
What class are you taking, Lastri?
Introduction to Communication.
-We are in the same class.
-Really?
Let's go to class.
This is our first day.
What are we going to do?
We are going to play a prank on someone.
Who am I going to prank this time?
Who is going to be my victim?
This is going to be fun. Stay tuned.
What are you doing?
I am planning a prank for my vlog.
That's disgusting.
Can you walk faster?
Reva?
Did you just wake up?
No, ma'am.
Just call me Lastri.
-Do you have class today?
-Yes.
What class?
Introduction to communication.
Good.
We are in the same class.
Come on. Wait, wait.
We have to fix your hair,
to make you look beautiful.
Come on.
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning.
I am Lastri.
Just call me Lastri, okay?
Hi, miss. I am Lastri.
-Good morning.
-Hi.
-Should I sit here?
-No, Grandma.
Just call me Lastri.
-Yes, Grandma Lastri.
-Without grandma, just Lastri.
Okay. You can't sit here, Lastri.
What's up with him?
He's weird. Just sit anyway.
No, no.
What is wrong with you?
No.
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning, sir.
Get ready for your first quiz.
What quiz? We just got the text book.
-Come on, it's our first day.
-Quiz, really?
Excuse me, sir.
This is our first day in class,
we haven't learned anything.
How can you quiz us?
Did you get the text book?
Yes.
-When was that?
-Last week.
So you had one week to read the book.
What's the problem?
Anyone ready for the quiz?
-What is with you?
-You're such a brown noser.
See? Some of you are ready for the quiz.
Okay. Let me ask you, guys.
Who is against the quiz?
Me! Me!
Me, guys.
See? There's only one thing to do.
No quiz!
No quiz! No quiz! No quiz!
No quiz! No quiz!
-Stop.
-No quiz! No quiz!
Oh, no!
Grandma!
Help!
Pull the chair out!
Come on, stand her up!
Silence!
I just want to be straight with you.
This is between me and you.
We are old.
I don't understand, what is it
that encourages you
to study in this faculty?
Do you really think you can
compete with these young people?
You're just going
to bring shame on yourself,
and make a mockery of this faculty,
which I built with hard work.
Mister Chaerul,
I'd like to enjoy my life to the maximum.
No one knows how long
they still have to live...
Don't you realize that...
I can't overturn the rectorate's decision
to accept a senior citizen like you
as a student?
But I am the dean here.
I have the right to decide
what kind of student
is allowed in my faculty.
So,
after the end of the semester,
if your grade is below average,
I will be forced to do something.
Do you understand?
Okay, I will prove to you
that I can get good grades.
And I will uphold the reputation
of your faculty.
Please sign this online petition.
I have put the link on it. Thanks.
Good morning, Grandma.
Just call me Lastri.
Lastri, please sign our petition.
-Against the spontaneous quiz.
-What is this?
I am with you on this.
I have put the link here,
open it from your cell phone...
-to support my online petition.
-I need a cell phone for that?
Yes.
-Can you show me? I don't know how.
-Okay.
Dear God.
You can't do it with that phone.
Just support us anyway.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
-Okay, then.
Yes, I have something new.
I have something interesting here.
I am going to interview the grandma
who went viral yesterday.
Who is that? It is Lastri.
The freshman at Berdosa, guys.
-Come on, Lastri.
-Yes?
Say, hi.
What is it?
Hi. Are they boys or girls?
We have thousands of boys and girls
at Baladanny.
Look, there are 1,200 boys and girls live.
Asolole, right?
-There are a lots of them.
-Sure.
No, my battery is low.
You have lots of friends.
They're not my friends,
they're my followers.
They follow my updates,
my daily activities.
They listen to my rants.
They're not your friends
but you share your feelings with them?
I see them as friends,
but they're not my real friends.
They're my followers.
Please sign the petition.
What is this?
Trash.
-What are you doing?
-This is trash.
What did you say?
I said, this is trash. You don't like it?
Of course not!
What's happening over there?
Erfan! We have to help Erfan.
Hi, guys.
Look, Grandma Lastri got hit!
Look, Lastri!
In the old days,
even the worst of the students,
never make trouble two days in a row.
Shame on you.
And you, when I was young,
the elders were a role model
to the young people.
So, this is why
you didn't attend class.
As a student, I have the freedom
to exercise democracy.
I can express whatever I want.
A student called me lazy,
so I punched him.
You talk about democracy
but you hit others who
don't share your opinion?
Do you really know the meaning
of democracy?
And you...
Yes, you.
I have to tell you the truth.
You do not belong here.
At the end of the semester,
if your grade is below average,
I will expel you.
I worked hard to build this faculty.
Sweat and tears. I won't let it go down.
Understood?
Dear God.
This is not a question and answer session!
-If I get...
-Enough!
What is this?
Please calm down, guys.
Mr. Chaerul is always like that.
It has to be his way.
Whatever he wants.
Guys, can I borrow your power bank?
You caused all of this.
Why did you have to make those flyers?
As a student I can express
whatever I feel.
No one said you can't.
But someone has to tell you
not to be lazy and stupid.
Don't call me stupid!
No one has a power bank?
Danny.
The world won't end
if your phone is off for a while.
Come on, stop it!
I need to go home.
Lastri!
Help!
Come on, guys. Help.
Mother.
How do you feel, Lastri?
I feel better, dear.
We need to take you
to the hospital, Lastri.
Maybe she has a concussion.
I'd be dead if I had a concussion.
Enough. You need to get out of here.
My mother needs to rest. Come on, out.
-See you, Lastri.
-Come on.
I have lived for more than 40 years,
never in my life,
have I called my mother by her name.
You've only known her for a week.
Where are your manners?
She asked us to call her Lastri.
What if she asked you to call her...
What is it you people call
someone these days?
-Guys?
-Bor.
-Coy?
Netizen is always right?
Okay, whatever that is.
So, you will call her whatever she wants?
-Yes, guys.
-What?
Okay, listen.
If something happens to her...
What are you laughing at?
-Nothing.
-This is serious.
If something happens to my mother
on campus,
I am going to sue all of you!
-Do you understand?
-Yes, guys.
-And you? You?
-Yes, we understand.
Good.
Crazy kids.
We have to avenge her.
What? Anna is right to be mad at us.
I'm not talking about Anna.
We have to avenge the boys who hit Lastri.
Do you agree?
I agree.
I agree. It's good for my content.
It's up to you guys.
I don't want to be a part of it. See you.
Hey, where's your loyalty?
Can I borrow your power bank, guys?
Please, guys.
You say that once again,
I'll punch your face. Come on.
I haven't charged my phone.
Okay, Baladanny, as promised...
This is so good.
We are going to avenge Lastri.
We're just waiting for Erfan. Where is he?
-Have you found them?
-Yes, they're over there.
There.
Go for it!
-This is good, guys.
-Erfan!
-He brought a wooden stick.
-What are you doing, Erfan?
Hey, what did you do to Lastri?
-Let's run!
-Where are you going? You want to run?
You don't have to hit him.
-I have to.
-Let him go.
Just go, Mas. Just go.
Hey, wait, wait!
Aren't you Angela? I met you at...
Ouch!
You were the one who told me
not to hit him.
It was an accident.
The moral of the story, guys:
violence will not solve a problem.
-Asolole?
-Come on, just go!
Assalamualaikum. I'm so hungry.
Sorry, I'm late. There was... Dear God!
What happened to you, Mother?
I smoked some pot,
and I fell from a motorcycle.
Dear God. Mother.
Ask for God's forgiveness.
Remember your age, Mom.
I'm kidding.
-What happened?
-Well, Mas,
Mother was involved in a fight.
What?
Pot is so much better than fighting.
Neither's good.
I am fine.
Didn't you look at yourself in the mirror?
Your face is swollen.
What if your eyes had got hit?
That is why I never agreed
for you to go to college.
What for?
Since when, does a mother has
to ask permission from her daughter?
You live in my house.
You have to follow our rules.
Right, dear?
I'm just going to keep quiet.
What is your problem?
My problem is, I am hungry.
I don't want to stay up,
waiting for someone
that might never come home.
Are you afraid that I am going to die?
Just like what happened to Rianti?
Mother.
You can't bring back the dead, mom.
Enough!
Anna.
You don't even want to hear her name.
I haven't finished talking, Anna!
Come back here!
Your wife is so stubborn.
Maybe she takes after the neighbors.
Because you're not like that.
Are you trying to be funny?
I'm just trying to have dinner...
Just finish your meal.
No one asked you to stop.
I am just a guest in this house!
My life is so hard, fish.
What a beautiful design, right guys?
Very professional.
This is Sara.
A young and talented designer.
Come on, say hi.
Hi, Baladanny.
Your sketch is really nice. Thank you.
-There are lots of questions.
-Read it.
Kak, how can I choose
the right fashion for me?
Dear?
Lastri.
You spent the night here again?
No.
Okay, then.
You smell bad for a pretty girl.
I am going to give you my perfume.
-Perfume?
-Yes.
So you'll smell nice.
Enough.
We have to put on some more
so you'll smell nice.
I think that's enough.
I smell nice already.
Nice, right?
You also have to fix your hair.
I think that's good.
-Thank you, Lastri.
-It's okay.
I have to go to class.
Sorry.
You smell like flowers
on a freshly dug grave.
Can you put your mouth to rest?
I like that. Playing hard to get.
Today, I'd like you to write an essay
that describes
a mass communication theory.
Go ahead. You may take out your laptop.
The grandma is using a typewriter, guys.
What are you doing?
I'm typing, Sir.
Yes, I can see that.
Then, why did you ask?
Don't you have a laptop?
Laptop? They're too expensive, Sir.
In my class, assignments
are to be submitted
as a soft copy. Not hard copies like this.
Why don't you use letter stickers?
Stick the letters one by one.
This is a college of communication.
Not a communication museum.
Seriously.
Lastri.
Let's do homework together, okay?
You can use my laptop.
-I can?
-Sure, you can.
Thank you, beautiful.
Let's go to my dorm.
It's just around here.
Guys, what's up? Can I join in?
Baladannies are crazy about Lastri.
That's crazy.
Lastri, say hi!
Hi!
Aselole!
We're going to my dorm, to do homework.
Wanna join us?
Come.
How about it, guys? Should we join them?
Wait for me, guys. Sarah.
You said you wanted to discuss patterns.
Dear?
-Lastri?
-What are you doing here?
Come to my dorm.
Better than sitting alone here.
Guys, do you think Reva will join us?
Hey, guys. Please.
-Come.
-Come on.
Come!
What about Erfan? Should we ask him?
He's part of the gang, guys.
Huh?
-Are we really a gang now?
-I'm serious, Lastri.
Good God! This is fun!
Aselole!
-Isn't this fun?
-We're a gang!
But, I don't want to get a tattoo.
Okay, Danny, go invite Erfan.
Message him, call him,
Instagram live, story, whatever. Come.
What was that?
Today I'm making a video
that's going to be my favorite.
Because this is how you find out
about one's personality.
Okay, so it's time to tour Sarah's room!
What is it?
Wrong room?
No. Wait a second.
Wait. Sorry.
This is so strange, guys.
What happened to her?
You're done?
Okay. Come in.
-May we?
-Yes, you may.
-We can come in, guys.
-Have a seat.
What happened?
It was too messy, Lastri.
So, I had to clean it up a bit.
This is so instagrammable, guys!
Guys, can I charge my phone?
The socket's right there.
You have a very nice room, Sarah.
What about you?
Do you live in a dorm, too?
Or do you live with your parents?
No.
Lastri, we should start doing
our homework.
-Yes, let's get started.
-Let's.
Anna, it's almost 9 p.m.
Mom hasn't returned?
Have you called her?
Her phone's inactive.
-Lastri.
-Yes?
How does it look? Do you need help?
No, I'm almost done.
That was quick, Lastri.
You taught me well.
Are you hungry? Let's order dinner.
No, I'm going to have dinner at home.
Oh, dear. Home! What time is it?
Oh, God! It's 9 p.m.!
My daughter will be waiting for me!
Lastri, wait!
Your mom has entrusted you to us.
Did my mom rise from the grave?
No! I meant Ibu Anna.
I'm afraid to get punished.
We'll take you home.
Danny, wake up.
-My followers...
-Ibu Anna will be furious! Hurry!
-Oh, no!
-Wake up!
Come on, hurry!
Let's go! Hurry!
Quick! Watch out!
Hurry up! Run!
Sorry, guys. I'm late.
Never mind, let's go.
What's happening?
What's going on?
Guys! Are you serious, guys?
-What is it?
-I can't drive, guys!
Danny! Get out!
Stupid!
Come on, hurry!
Guys, our mission tonight
is to take Lastri home.
Isn't it crazy? We're really good friends.
Oh, no!
Anna!
Amri!
Climb the fence. It's not that high.
Are you serious?
Let's do it, guys.
Hold this.
-Dear God.
-Dear God is right.
Help us out, guys.
-I'm not strong enough.
-Danny, get over there. Hop over.
Yes! Pull her from the other side.
You do that! I'm supporting the foot!
Hurry up! How can Lastri jump
if you do it like that?
It's hard, guys!
You can do it. You're flexible!
It's hard.
Hey, Anna!
You're mad, aren't you?
Should I jump now?
Aselole!
Coming home late,
not answering your phone...
Why are you so reckless?
Mom, what do you have to say?
Calm down, Anna.
I was invited to Sarah's dorm.
Look what you've done, Sarah.
Such a provocateur! You were there, too.
Aunty, I'm sorry. I was just...
Stop.
Enough excuses. I don't want to hear it.
Mom, why is your phone switched off?
It ran out of juice.
I wanted to charge it but the socket
was used by Danny for his phone.
No shame, Danny!
What a crime.
It's not like that, guys!
My name is Anna, not guys.
-It's not like that, Anna.
-It's Mrs. Anna.
You're so inconsiderate.
Why do you call the elderly
by their names?
Mrs. Anna.
Mom, you can call me Anna.
Anna, don't overreact.
Overreact?
Mom, I nearly had a heart attack.
I can't wait like this anymore. I can't.
That's it. You can't come home
so late at night.
And don't hang out with them.
I forbid you.
I don't want to be restrained.
They're my friends.
Right, gang?
-Gang?
-Yes, gang.
Oh my God, Mom!
No, Aunty. It's not really a gang.
It's more like...
Squad, guys.
-No.
-No, it's not.
-Study group!
-Too tacky.
Community.
That's too outdated, guys!
-Gang is better.
-I agree, gang.
-Squad!
-Gang is better.
-Yes.
-Enough!
As long as you live in this house,
you have to follow my rules, and Amri's.
That's it.
I'm butting out of this!
Well then, I am moving out
from this house.
I don't want to be restrained.
Yes, gang? Am I right?
Aselole!
-Yes.
-Aselole! Aselole!
Anna, I'll come by tomorrow
to pack my belongings.
Why not now? We'll wait for you.
Tomorrow, it is.
Now is not a good time.
Ibu Anna is still mad.
It's cooler like this anyway.
Leaving like the good guys in movies.
You heard them. See you tomorrow.
So, Lastri will be more independent now.
-Come on, Lastri. Come on!
-Watch out!
Careful.
The writing is too small. I can't read it.
It's switched off again. Come on, Mom!
Amri!
Mom, where are you going?
Come home, Mom!
Anna misses you.
And so do I.
This is the moment of truth.
We will find out our GPA
for this semester.
Let's do it together. One...
Two...
Three.
Don't call it out just yet.
We'll wait for Lastri.
Wow.
Lastri in the house, guys!
Thank God!
My prayers are answered! I got 1.3!
What's yours?
I got 2.7.
Mine is 2.5, guys.
I got 2.8.
I got 3.9.
-That's so high.
-One point three!
I am the stupidest!
I will be kicked out by Chaerul.
Lastri, it's okay.
I have an idea.
We're going to voodoo that puffer fish.
No. Not that extreme.
We're going to make him attracted to you.
No. Out of the question.
-No.
-Lastri.
This is so you won't be expelled.
He is lonely.
A widower. Divorced ten years ago.
Because his wife was sane enough.
Who wants to marry a hater like him?
Lastri, you know the term "hater"?
Well, she likes doing
Instagram live with me.
Ugh!
That's not important. Let's focus.
Today Lastri, Sarah, and I,
are going to do a social experiment.
We're going to test out if men can still
be tricked by women's looks.
Since men are more visual beings,
looks really matter.
That's not me.
This suits you best.
Our dean likes a woman
who is graceful and a bit arrogant.
How do you know so much about him?
Honorable, Mr. Dean...
Just use his name, don't use his title.
Mr. Chaerul.
Don't be too formal.
Bro Chaerul.
You're Lastri, right?
Don't panic, stay relaxed. Chill.
Yes, Bro.
Here's the thing, Bro.
I need to talk to you.
Are you free?
He won't resist an invitation
to a fancy restaurant.
Flamboyan is a fancy restaurant.
Especially if it's on you. Free meal.
Your treat, okay?
Remember, be arrogant.
Money is not a problem, Bro.
Don't act like you don't have any, Bro.
What do you say?
All right, then.
Okay, then.
You seem very hungry.
I might order more dishes.
Yes, sure.
Welcome, Sir.
Not too many.
Okay.
-I want black coffee.
-Okay.
And...
Some fruit.
Okay.
So...
What's the reason for this invitation?
Just tell the truth.
Be honest.
Because he is arrogant, definitely.
Undoubtedly stubborn.
Egotistical, needless to say.
But dad doesn't like liars.
I knew it!
Well...
My GPA this semester was awful.
I beg you, please...
Don't expel me.
Give me a chance to make things right.
Why do I have to give you a chance?
Riyanti...
My only grandchild.
She had a dream.
She wanted to go to college in Europe
majoring in communications.
She studied every night and day.
And finally...
She received a scholarship.
But...
She got into an accident and passed away.
I don't know.
Did God love her so much
that He took her away or maybe...
God hates me.
That I...
Had to bury my own grandchild.
But I'm still not ready
to bury her dreams.
You should be realistic.
If you're not able...
But I am. Give me a chance.
What if...
your GPA is still awful?
I'll kick myself out.
Okay, then.
But, under one condition.
If you want more dishes,
I can't pay for them.
-No. Not that.
-What?
I'd like to...
invite you to dinner tomorrow.
That's it? Yes.
Yesterday,
I took you to a fancy restaurant.
Yet, you take me to place like this.
I'm all dressed up for a place like this.
But it's good, right?
The tempeh is good.
You were there until evening?
Besides being arrogant, he's also cheap?
Such a sly bureaucrat.
He's definitely arrogant.
He is definitely cheap.
He is also definitely a bureaucrat.
But...
Mr. Chaerul is not sly.
You sound so in love.
-Oh, my God. That can't be happening.
-Lastri, so how did it go?
Are you expelled?
I got a second chance!
I have to hurry to class.
I have plans this evening with Chaerul.
Dinner at a fancy restaurant.
If this were a movie,
this would be a plot twist.
Instead of unfollowing the Dean,
she is subscribing to him instead .
-What's going on?
-Okay then. I'm off as well.
Where to? We have class.
I need to do something.
I'll catch up with you later.
Sarah! Erfan!
As mentioned in the first point,
journalism is fundamentally...
delivering the truth.
That's the difference
between journalism and hoax.
Journalism is also committed
to the masses.
-Yes?
-Pardon me, Sir.
Shouldn't class be over at 4 p.m.?
Because I have an appointment at 6 p.m.
Well, it's only 5 p.m.
Well, I have to get ready and dress up.
You're right.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
So, may I?
Of course...
not. Wait until I'm finished.
Oh, you!
Yes, all of you.
Describe the points above.
Lastri, do you want
to jump out the window?
Danny.
Lastri wants to jump out of the window.
Okay, then.
Hey!
Are you running away?
Do you not realize
we're on the third floor?
Shall we continue, guys?
Come in.
Good afternoon, Sir.
What happened?
Regarding your instruction
at the beginning of this semester.
If Lastri acts up,
I am supposed to take her directly to you.
So, here she is.
Yes. So, what happened?
She attempted to run away
through the window.
From the third floor.
Through the window? That's pretty extreme.
The class was supposed
to be over at 4 p.m., Sir.
But Mr. Fahmi extended his lecture.
Meanwhile, I have plans
with a special person.
But that is my right as a lecturer, Sir.
Are you asking me to cancel my plans
with this special someone?
You're too much.
There's no such thing as a special person.
But there is a special martabak, though.
A person can't be special.
Why not?
There are many special people.
You act like you know a lot.
What I mean is the use of the word
"special" here is...
Quiet, please?
You may go home now.
Thank you, Sir. I can't wait
to meet that special someone.
Good luck.
Have fun.
That look on Fahmi's face...
I was also offended.
How come he didn't believe
that I'm a special person?
Yeah. That's how it is.
The problem with people like us.
What?
We easily get offended.
It's such a pity.
I pity the people around us.
Pity?
Fahmi is my subordinate.
That's his consequence.
I'm not talking about Fahmi.
It's about your daughter.
You know?
Sarah is trying hard...
so that no one knows I'm her father.
Actually, there's a cold war
between Sarah and I.
I just want her to take a proper major.
Instead, she wants to learn about fashion.
That's not useful.
You know what?
There are three photos of you
in Sarah's room.
-Three photos of me?
-Yes.
No way!
Why does she choose photos
over her real father?
Well, because your photos are not stubborn
and annoying.
Dad.
Have a seat, Dad.
I was tidying up our house.
Then I found your childhood photos.
You were so cute!
I wanted to put your photos
in my workplace.
You don't need to worry.
No one will recognize you.
You were still a baby in those photos.
Yeah, sure.
But, would you like to...
put my photo in your bedroom?
So, we're even!
No! What for?
Why? Are you ashamed of being my daughter?
No. It's not because I feel ashamed.
Then why?
Because you're annoying, Dad.
Why are you laughing?
I've heard that phrase twice today.
Who's the other person who said that?
That Old Hag.
Guys, I'm so happy
because it's my first time
going to a night club.
Discotheque and karaoke.
Can you guess where am I?
Asolole. I'm so excited.
-I'm going to...
-Dan, I want to address your followers.
Okay. Gladly, guys.
What's the name?
Baladanny.
You're all stupid!
What's wrong, guys?
Dan, do you understand
the meaning of guys?
I'm here alone.
Guys is for plural. Get it?
Nice info, guys. Asolole.
Being friends with a former
boy band is so hard.
Come in, please.
VIP room, guys.
The first hour is 150,000 rupiah,
excluding food and drinks.
For an additional--
Sir, is there a girl named Reva here?
If I'm not mistaken, I saw her here.
She's a Berdosa like us.
Son, we all sin.
But if we mean it,
Insha Allah,
the gate of repentance will open.
Oh, my!
Sir,
I want a karaoke companion
who can be my date. Do you have one?
Oh, my God!
We just talked about repentance.
Thank you for your good influence
towards my daughter.
Sarah is already a good girl
before she met me.
You're the one who taught
your daughter to be a good person.
Sometimes your mouth
can be sweet. Sometimes bitter.
-My mouth is not coffee.
-That's right.
Both your mouth and coffee
give people insomnia.
Sweet talker.
Such sweet talk!
I'm serious.
I want to spend time with you
again tomorrow.
Food addiction? You're greedy.
No, I'm not.
-Then what?
-Dance addiction.
You can dance by yourself.
I can't.
How can I dance without a partner?
What do you say?
Okay. Tomorrow, right?
Your favorite lecturer is calling me.
Fahmi.
Hello?
What's going on?
WhatsApp link chat?
About what? Okay, wait a minute.
-Yes.
-Open the door.
Hi, ladies. Come in.
This is Yolanda, this is Baby.
-This is Mawar and this is Angela.
-Hi.
Enjoy.
I think I know her, guys.
Reva.
Wait. Angela!
Guys, Lastri is having a makeover.
She's really into it.
Be careful, Lastri.
You might end up liking him.
God forbid! I don't like that puffer fish!
If it weren't for the grade,
I wouldn't do it!
Hey! So, is this the reason
you're always sleepy?
What do you care?
What I do is none of your business!
You consider this a job?
I thought you weren't stupid.
-Not that stupid?
-Yes. You're smart!
You're stupid for choosing this job.
What do you know about this job?
You don't know, do you?
Do you know how it feels
doing this job every day?
You don't know!
Just get out. I have a job to do.
Don't disturb me anymore!
You want to do your job?
Take this 100,000 rupiah! Go home now.
You've got your money for tonight.
You got what you wanted.
Oh, God! She slapped him.
I told you to go! Go!
Get away from here now!
Amazing! This is good, guys!
Be sensitive, jerk!
I still have to pay installments
on that phone, guys!
Chaerul, wait.
Wait. Let me explain.
Let me explain.
From now on, stay away from my daughter.
I pity you.
Pity?
Are you God? Don't be like a saint!
God doesn't pity me and my grandchild!
She doesn't need pity. She's gone.
They're happy wherever they are.
You need to pity yourself
and your daughter who are left behind.
My daughter and I are fine.
Are you sure?
This is the real world, Lastri,
not a fairy tale.
So, "everything is fine" is impossible.
Starting tomorrow, don't come to class.
Reva!
You have a letter from the Dean.
YOU ARE REQUIRED TO ATTEND
STUDENT ETHICS SUMMON
BECAUSE YOUR ATTITUDE
DISGRACES OUR REPUTATION
Riyanti!
We have to accept this sincerely.
We have to.
You guys know?
Yes, guys.
Lastri, I will talk to my father.
You don't need to. This is my fault.
No.
We need to protest.
Don't do that, Fan.
This is my problem.
Don't make it everyone's problem.
Guys, if we make this issue viral...
This is because of you!
Why is it because of me, guys?
Stop it.
Hey. Where's Reva?
-Reva, come down!
-Come down, Reva.
Come down!
-Reva, come down!
-Come on, come down!
-Reva!
-Reva, come down!
-Move, guys!
-Make way!
-Reva!
-Oh, my God!
Reva, what are you doing?
-Reva!
-Reva, come down!
Reva!
Reva, come down!
What's wrong?
What's happening?
Do any of you know what's happening?
I don't know, guys.
Tell her!
Why me, guys?
Reva and Lastri's issues
are because of your social media!
I was just telling the truth.
Baladannies deserves to know this.
I'm doing God's work here.
You're not a journalist.
You're just overacting to become famous!
-I'm overacting?
-Yes, you're overacting.
Who do you think you are? An activist?
You're easily triggered.
You act like you're the best.
Stop it!
-Don't get mad at me, guys!
-So what?
-I'm not afraid of you!
-Enough! Stop it!
Why are you fighting?
Look, she's in danger. You go up there!
Go there!
Why me?
You can do it, guys!
Reva!
-Be careful!
-Be careful, Fan!
-Guys!
-Reva!
Be careful.
Shit!
What are you doing here?
What about you? Don't ask me.
Bismillah.
I hope Erfan can convince Reva.
If you want to jump, then do it.
Don't make a drama.
Who wants to jump?
So what are you doing here?
I needed a quiet place to think.
A quiet place?
Ever tried going to the cemetery
at midnight?
Are you crazy?
Why would you consider this tower
a quiet place?
You're making my life very hard.
Hard? What do you know about a hard life?
-You come from a rich family.
-Hey!
Don't ever think rich people
have a happy life.
Do you want to know how hard my life is?
Listen.
Me and my mother just found out
my father has a second wife.
I never knew who my father was,
since I was kid.
My father married a girl my age.
And she was my ex-girlfriend.
So, my ex is my step-mother.
Can you imagine?
My life is like a soap opera.
My mom was a gudeg seller.
She fell in love with an Italian tourist
and he dumped her when she was pregnant.
She was so heartbroken, she passed away.
Now I live alone.
Oh, my God!
My mother...
Okay, you win.
Your soap opera is better than mine.
Exactly.
Like a tormented movie. Oh, my God!
Rev.
Sorry, because of my carelessness
and Danny's...
Everyone knows your job.
I know how to take care of myself
doing those kinds of jobs.
Not everyone who works those
kinds of jobs are easy girls.
Reva, come down!
Miss Reva! Mr. Erfan!
Please come down! This is an order!
If there are casualties
due to your stupid actions,
the reputation of our college will suffer.
Let's have a bit of fun.
How?
Miss Reva! Mr. Erfan! Please come down!
Sir!
Reva wants to jump.
Don't do that! Come down!
Don't jump, guys!
Don't jump!
Every problem can be solved.
Don't worry. Tell me your problem.
What's your problem?
Why put eye drops in?
Oh, my God.
This life is so cruel.
I can't bear it anymore.
-Mr. Erfan.
-I will jump right now!
-Don't! Reva!
-Don't jump, guys!
Hey!
Oh, my God! Reva!
You guys down there,
don't attempt to catch me.
What do you mean?
Let my body break into pieces.
Let my head crack and my brain scatter.
My intestines splatter,
and my kidneys crush. Let it be!
Enough. You sound so stupid.
Don't jump. I'll help you.
I'll help solve your problem.
What's your problem?
Say it.
Sir, please don't expel me and Lastri.
Is that it?
-Say it.
-Okay.
One more thing, Sir.
What else?
Get rid of spontaneous quizzes.
I agree, guys!
Fine, just get down.
I'll see what I can do.
Now come down. Hurry!
Asolole!
Asolole, guys.
Guys, come down.
-Thank God!
-My jargon, guys. Asolole!
Asolole. Come down, guys.
It's hot up there. Hurry.
My jargon, guys.
Mr. Dean, could I...
have an audience?
Don't call him Mr. Dean.
Don't call him Mr. Dean, guys.
Guys, I also wanna listen.
Can I, Mr. Chaerul?
Why don't you ask your media team
to come in?
Let them stay outside.
What do you want from me?
Lastri wants to apologize, Dad.
I'm sorry.
Say it. Hurry.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
Heartache?
I'm a divorcee.
I'm divorced and I have a daughter
who left the house.
She doesn't want anyone to know
that I'm her father.
I'm a heartbreak master.
I'm an old widow.
My husband passed away.
My only granddaughter...
passed away.
My son-in-law...
snores loudly.
Well, I too
am a heartbreak master.
So?
Now we know
each other's feelings,
what do you want, then?
Remind you of your promise.
Promise?
What promise?
You invited me to a dance...
tonight.
How dare you ask me to dance?
I'm still angry.
What if I reject your request?
I'm a heartbreak master, did you forget?
Huh.
What are you doing?
I can't hear them. Shut up!
What if...
What if I accepted your request?
What would the song be?
What's wrong with your hands?
Music, please!
Play the music.
What song is that?
What?
Is that?
I don't know, guys.
Turn off my phone, guys.
Oh, God!
My name is Lastri.
This is the ending of my story.
UNIVERSITY CYBER INDONESIA
Riyanti.
BORN 10 FEBRUARY 2001
DIED 21 MAY 2019
Your grandmother has done it.
Riyanti,
we promise we'll take care
of Lastri until she graduates.
At this age...
there are so many new things
that I don't know,
which I can still learn.
I learned that losing someone
isn't a reason to stop.
But losing someone is a reason
to keep moving on.
Dancing.
Because one day...
The song will stop.
So, enjoy it as long as you can.
Come on!
Next time, be careful who you prank.
She's elderly.
Sorry, it was unintentional, guys.
Help her. One, two, three.
One, two, three.
-Failed.
-Try again.
You go up there. Tell her to come down.
I'm afraid of heights.
I don't want to fall from there.
You have health insurance.
That's not useful.
Well, if you fall and die...
You'll die as a martyr.
You'll go to heaven.
I'm moving out...
I can't... I'm sorry.
You just woke...
Grandma is asking... Grandmother?
Riyanti, my granddaughter...
It's not working.
So...
Oh, God!
Let's go, guys.
Thank you, Amri.
-Assalamualaikum.
-Wa'alaikumsalam.
-What's wrong?
-It's stuck.
I will drive your car.