The world of warrior
is like a long and deep tunnel.
With the threat of death forever looming
in the darkness.
A constant struggle,
one fight after another,
each of them ending with a death.
Must that be the warrior's way?
To kill or to be killed.
To my mind,
The reason to master such skills
is not to become a perfect killer.
But to be able to defend the weak
and the powerless.
What is the meaning of such perfection.
If it's not used
for the benefit of humankind?
So when a duel ends
with a rival's death
it's only loss that I feel.
All the more so, as time goes by.
There's much I've lost,
but I have also gained.
My four students, for instance.
Three are the children of
rivals I was forced to kill.
Merah Dara,
my younger female student,
is the daughter of Beling Ungu.
Daya Gerhana,
is the daughter of Golok Wangi.
Kala Biru,
my oldest and most able student,
is the son of Gagak Hitam.
All three are here because
of my feelings of guilt.
But Lembah Angin, my youngest student,
is here to remind me of my greatest sin
I found him.
He had been abandoned.
What if I were your enemy?
If such were the case,
only Biru and Angin would still
be standing.
I can't say it enough
the greater a fighter's skill,
the more often he'll be attacked
from behind.
That's enough training for today.
Biru, Gerhana
I want you to go
to the battle arena.
Pay my respects to members
of the High Council
and also to the winner.
We will, Guru.
All of you.
We'll meet again tonight.
There's something I want to tell you.
Yes, Guru.
The time has come.
The Next challenger.
Cempaka's best students
are here again to be mere spectators.
Any more challengers?
Your time is near, Biru.
Once again, the winner of the battle
is the House of Red Wing.
The Honorable High Council,
we ask that you present the victory cloth.
As students of Golden Cane House,
we express our congratulations
to The House of Red Wing.
Our guru, Cempaka,
sends you her greetings.
Thank you.
Cempaka always sends her students
to watch Red Wing wins.
This is an honor for us.
It is we who learn by watching,
it is we who are indebted.
Once again,
congratulations to the House of Red Wing.
It's time for us to go home.
It will be dark soon.
Stay here for the night.
Thank you,
but another time, perhaps.
Guru Cempaka wants us to return home.
Give my greetings to her.
Thank you. We will.
I don't fear death.
No knowledge in existence
can prevent a person,
from escaping death.
Biru,
Gerhana,
Dara, and Angin.
Although you are not my own children,
you know that I have been
a mother for you.
Though all of you are skilled fighters,
I must ask,
is there one among you
who can resist being a victor?
Because, victory in any field
has no meaning
if it comes from
another person's demise.
Today,
I will give my golden cane to one of you,
But I hope all of you will continue
to serve this House.
To that same person
I will also teach the move known as
Golden Cane Encircles the Earth.
That is the ultimate move,
the undefeatable move.
You must know,
The beauty of this cane,
is nothing when compared with its power.
That is why this cane
must never fall into the wrong hands.
One of you will inherit this cane.
I've thought about this a long time.
I am giving it to Dara.
But, Guru...
I've spoken.
And you've heard what I said.
There's no turning the world back in time.
Accept your duty.
Even With this cane in your hand,
It will not be easy.
To teach Dara the move,
I will take her away for some time,
to train her.
I will take Angin as well to help me
with my remedy.
Biru,
Gerhana.
Watch over this place until we return.
We will, Guru.
Now leave me here with Dara.
Hold tightly.
Concentrate your thoughts.
Shield your mind from false voices.
Now, there is something else
I must tell you.
It's too late.
Give me the golden cane.
The poison should have worked faster
so she could die peacefully in the House.
You two need to know that
we did this to prevent her
from making an even worse mistake.
She's confused. Addled.
I truth is I wish you could be the one.
Run. Get out of here.
Who are you?
Where is my brother? Where is my cane?
Angin!
Tell her to eat.
Are you sure it's not poisoned?
Do you trust him?
Angin,
we must avenge our teacher's death.
Listen to me.
Guru Cempaka told me something
the night before she died.
She said that if anything happened to her
before she could teach me the final move,
I was to find a warrior
by the name of Naga Putih.
She said that he is the only
other person who has mastered that move.
You know of this?
We convey our condolences for the death
of your teacher, Cempaka
and the loss of the golden cane as well.
We never would have thought,
they would poison her
and steal the golden cane.
Mobilize our students
to track down Dara and Angin.
Yes, Guru.
Cempaka's death is a tragic loss
for the world of warriors.
Thank you for saying so.
That is actually the reason
we've come here.
Our teacher greatly respected you.
We hope that you will permit us
to join The Red Wing House.
To have Cempaka's students here
would be a great honor.
Convey this sad news to the High Council.
Prepare the finest of burial ceremonies.
This will serve as a measure
of our final respect
for Cempaka, the Golden Cane Warrior.
Our House will reward anyone who is able
to help Biru and Gerhana
retrieve the golden cane.
The cane is Biru's by right.
Yes, Guru.
Any regrets?
Regrets? None at all.
Don't force your body.
Your body needs time to recover.
I am going away for a few days.
You and your brother may stay here
until you have recovered.
We share in your grief
for Cempaka's passing.
Our House will help to avenge the pain
that Dara and Angin caused.
Thank you. You show us great honor.
Wherever they've hidden,
we'll find them.
Just be patient.
We trust you, Guru.
And no matter what happens,
we'll always be grateful
for being allowed to join your House.
Your new fellow students
will help you find Dara and Angin.
And once you catch them,
I will not interfere with you in
how you want to settle the score.
That matter I leave entirely to you.
You don't have to serve me.
There are other students who can do that.
This is but a sign of thanks
for accepting us
and appointing us as your lead students.
I see that Cempaka taught you
more than just to fight,
she taught you to be
a good person as well.
My respect for her excellence.
It's Elang. Elang's here.
My brother and I don't know
how to repay you for all you've done.
You were in trouble.
It was our duty to help.
Don't worry. You're safe here.
Do you know where to find Naga Putih?
How did you know that
we're looking for Naga Putih?
Just who are you, anyway?
This should tell you that
you still need a lot more training.
Tomorrow I have to go away again,
it's up to you.
Go on looking for Naga Putih
not knowing where he is,
or wait for me to take you to him.
Angin.
It's Elang.
This is the third time I've come.
Now pay your debt.
Angin!
We have to help the villagers.
Do you know this person?
She's not here.
Where is she?
Where have you hidden her?
Dara!
Angin!
Come out!
Or we'll burn this place down!
Stop!
Please forgive me.
Forgive us.
None of this would have happened
if we hadn't been here.
Where is Angin?
He gave himself up
to save the people here.
The attackers left a message.
Biru is waiting for you at the House.
Angin can be traded for the golden cane.
Biru promised not to involve
the other Houses.
Again, forgive me,
but now I must try to save Angin.
This time listen and trust me.
You don't know enough yet
to save yourself,
let alone to save Angin.
Maybe you are a great fighter,
and I am the reason
for the disturbance here.
But you have no right
to judge my capabilities.
And definitely no right to prevent me
from trying to save Angin.
Say something.
I know you can talk.
Tell me where Dara is,
and the golden cane.
Tell me and I'll give you
the chance to live
and to know how it feels to be an adult.
You're just a kid.
You don't know what Gerhana and I feel.
Cempaka killed our parents,
then took us to be her students.
And just when we were starting to enjoy
the fame and the power
of Golden Cane House.
She shut it down
and moved us to this dump of a place.
After all that time
serving the Golden Cane,
look at what happened.
Tell me where to find Dara
and the golden cane, Angin.
Once it is in my hand,
I will bring back to this House
the fame and power Cempaka disavowed.
And I will give you an honorable position.
You took an oath, Elang.
I know that you could help Dara,
but not in this battle.
Dara will not be able
to defend herself alone.
We can only wait and see.
If they should die,
you know what you have to do.
Right now, the important thing
is the villagers' safety.
You must lead them to a safer place.
It's Dara and the golden cane.
I have no time
for small talk with you, Gerhana.
Where is Angin?
Is this what you're looking for?
Do you want the cane?
Then release Angin.
The cane is mine, you should know that.
You'll never be the Golden Cane Warrior.
No one ever will.
The only true heir was the one
you have killed cowardly.
Stupid girl.
I am far more skilled than you, Dara.
I'm not going to attack
because you point that cane at me.
Its power doesn't depend
on the final move.
Take this useless kid,
and give the cane to me.
Untie him.
Angin.
Angin, Dara.
Where are you?
Show your faces
and let me send your souls to heaven.
It's only me here.
So, you can speak after all.
The good of heart wants nothing,
though he could have it all.
The small of heart wants everything
but will gain nothing.
It's a waste of time looking for her.
Let the weakling rot
wherever she's hiding.
I'm glad to see the golden cane
is back in your hands.
Cempaka can now rest more calmly.
We have you to thank for that.
Even so, you still have to find Dara.
No matter what,
you can't let her remain free.
We won't, Guru.
The villagers who sheltered them
also bear responsibility.
We'll see they pay as well.
If I should die,
I want you to lead this House.
Show this place the same respect
like Cempaka did with her Golden Cane.
I will, Guru.
But please, Guru,
don't speak of death again.
How much longer?
Tonight's cup of tea
should keep him from waking again.
Take them down.
I have important announcements to make.
Henceforth, Biru replaces Cempaka
as Warrior of the Golden Cane.
This House shall now go
by the name of The Golden Cane.
And there will be no more competitions
in the arena
because no one can defeat
the Golden Cane Warrior.
Spread this news to all fighters
and their Houses,
Golden Cane will be the highest
and most powerful House.
Let no one dare to try to stop this.
But, Biru...
Call him “Guru”.
But Guru, the High Council...
There is no High Council any more.
Just as Biru said,
Golden Cane is now the highest authority.
I'm sorry but I had to do that.
I should have helped you
when you tried to save Angin,
but I couldn't.
I wasn't allowed to help.
Tell me who you are.
I want to know your story.
That and your relationship
with Naga Putih.
Naga Putih left this world some time ago.
I will tell you everything.
I can't kill anymore.
Not even the blackest of souls.
Your decision means that
more victims will fall.
The weak and the powerless.
The innocent and the defenseless.
Retire after you have mastered
the ultimate move.
Forgive me, Guru.
I will not change my mind.
Cempaka is capable
of following my footsteps.
To her I shall give the golden cane.
It's fitting that she be given it
and to lead this House.
This isn't just about
who gets the golden cane.
The move of the
Golden Cane Encircles the Earth,
can only be done in pairs.
If the House is to live on,
you must find two students
who are able to master it.
Don't die before that happens.
You, too, Naga Putih,
must pass on your knowledge to
at least two students.
The power of the golden cane
must not be lost.
Your knowledge endows you
with responsibility.
I understand, Guru.
I will pass down the knowledge.
Make sure you choose the right person.
Now you two go
and settle your personal affairs.
And don't come back until you do.
Cempaka.
Do you still want to lead the House,
to keep on fighting, and to leave me?
Won't you change your mind?
It's not just because I'm unable
to ignore the teacher's request.
It's my conscience, Naga,
a voice inside telling me that
I must continue this noble task.
Well then, warrior,
I ask you to swear to
never come looking for me.
In turn, I will swear that,
neither I nor our son will ever bother
you or intervene in your affairs.
Swear this to me, Cempaka.
I swear.
And so you are...
I am the son of Naga Putih and Cempaka.
The sole owner to knowledge
of the golden's cane's ultimate move.
Dara,
just as my father once swore.
I, too, was made to swear that
I would not intervene
in this affair of yours.
Forgive me for being unable to help
when you tried to save Angin.
Now I see,
why Cempaka asked Angin to come
when she was going to teach me that move.
Angin was to learn it, too, because
the move can only be done in pairs.
I was my father's only student.
He was my pair.
Now, I have just one duty.
To ensure sure that the final move is
passed onto Cempaka's choice of student.
If she died before she could pass it on.
Elang, accept me as your student.
Help me to perfect my skills and to pass
on to me knowledge of the ultimate move.
Help me to avenge
the deaths of Cempaka and Angin.
I will follow your instructions.
Mastery of the final move requires
more than just two skilled warriors.
The two must be able to unify
their thoughts and breath as one.
Much time and patience
will be needed to master the move.
For Cempaka, Angin and all warriors
who gave this cane its value and meaning.
Unite the two of us to
so that we can retrieve the cane.
Before she died,
Cempaka often went off by herself.
I think now that she was looking for you.
All that is past now.
It will be night soon.
You've mastered all the basic moves.
Tomorrow we'll start to practice
the ultimate move.
Forces of evil now control
the world of warriors.
We must combine
forces and launch a joint attack.
No, that will only diminish our defenses.
Golden Cane House
is too large and powerful.
Most other Houses have joined with them
to share in the power of Biru
and the golden cane.
We'll send another warrior.
For the third time
in as many months yet,
another fool has tried to kill me
and take the golden cane.
I am the rightful heir
of the golden cane.
With this cane,
I guarantee the power and fame of
this place within the world of warriors.
Anyone who dares defy me,
will meet their death.
We may have killed Cempaka too soon.
I have yet to discover
the power of this cane.
Without knowledge of the ultimate move,
this cane is no different from any other.
Biru,
Cempaka took that knowledge to her death.
There's nothing to regret.
No one else can possibly
know of it either.
Even without the golden cane,
you are an incredible fighter.
Invincible.
And with the golden cane in your hand,
everyone will submit to you.
But I think the elders are suspicious.
Then it's time to finish them off.
They're the main obstacle.
Useless old men.
Dark forces have controlled
the warriors' world
for so long now.
We are all paralyzed.
And, yet, Biru and Gerhana
remain undefeated.
Dara is ready, Uncle.
We now have the chance
to bring them down
and to retrieve the golden cane.
If you have decided to serve
as Dara's pair in fighting them,
you will betray your oath.
I was the witness,
when you swore to your father that,
you would not intervene.
You know the penalty, Elang.
But the interests of the majority
are greater than my own.
I have no other choice.
Concentrate your mind.
The time has arrived.
Guru.
What is it?
Two outsiders are causing a disturbance
in the arena.
Stop!
Who are you?
Why are you causing a disturbance
for no reason?
There's a reason, Biru.
We're here to meet you and Gerhana.
The time has come for you to return
the golden cane to its rightful owner.
You're out of your mind.
Biru is the rightful owner
of the golden cane.
I've come here to recover my right,
the Golden Cane.
Without bloodshed.
If you refuse to give it to me,
I challenge you to a fair fight.
Just the two of you
against the two of us,
with no outside help.
In the same arena you closed down
after you stole the golden came from me.
All of you, listen to me.
We accept the challenge.
None of you are to interfere.
It's only right that this woman
who killed our teacher
and our brother Angin.
She should die in our hands.
Mother.
Not in front of your daughter, Gerhana.
There's only one place
to finish this fight.
I can finish you off anywhere.
You're using moves of the golden cane.
Dara couldn't have taught them to you.
Who are you?
The golden cane is now back
in your hands, Dara.
Your teacher and Angin
did not die in vain.
Your mother and Angin, Elang.
Your mother.
Yes, my mother.
A true warrior holds true
to his promises, Elang.
Yet to be true means
to live in a silent world.
I understand, Uncle.
Having betrayed my oath,
I must pay the penalty.
The world of the warrior
is like a long and deep tunnel.
Wherever you turn,
all you find is the threat of death
in the darkness.
And while there is light at the end of
even the longest and darkest of tunnels.
But whether that light
represents hope or menace,
one can never know.